What's going on?
Believers?
Doubters?
Anyone in between?
Y'all are talking shit about how blind I am.
And to that I say... I don't care.
I don't care.
I don't care at all.
You know what?
Maybe I'll rage spade more on purpose this time.
You guys didn't enjoy my unintentional rage spades?
Well, here comes the intentional rage spade!
You can't get it now!
I'm just kidding.
I'm gonna do my best as always.
By the way, when I wrote that message in the discord, this is pretty much me saying, no, please, please don't, you know, leave these 10 boxes at my doorstep.
Otherwise, I will be forced to go down to the store and grab a bag of candy.
I don't would hate that.
I'm enabling you guys to enable me, okay?
I thought to myself, you know what?
I probably shouldn't.
But if I make it about getting diorites, well, then it's not me who decided it, right?
You decided it.
I didn't do it.
I'm not addicted.
I can control it.
You should try a geometry dash.
Oh, yeah, you should try dashing geometry.
No, I have heard about that game, but it's like a very platformy game, right?
I heard it's very difficult.
I don't think it's something for me, though.
I saw some gameplay of it.
I don't know.
Maybe.
Maybe I'll try it one day.
It's like a rhythm game.
Yeah, okay.
Can you say pick my most beautiful side in Dutch, please?
I guess.
There we go.
That's my best attempt.
I have no idea what Dutch sounds like.
All I know is that it sounds like you're, you know, just taking a bunch of words and then just throwing them inside the mouth.
That's what it sounds like.
Like the sentence were just thrown down there, you know?
What does that even mean?
I don't want answers, Salar.
I'm not interested in it.
I just want to play the game.
And I'm going to play it my way, whether or not that's slow or fast, if it's smart or not.
I will say this.
I only have like 30 hours in this game at this point, okay?
I don't have a thousand hours like you guys, so don't expect me to know things.
I will figure it out.
It just takes a while, okay?
And if you don't think it's going to take a while, then you must be new here.
All right, it's going to be fine.
Don't worry.
It's going to be okay.
All right, let's get into it.
It's also kind of getting... hold on a minute.
Where's my... where is my audio thingy?
There it is.
I really need to invest in some kind of audio physical hardware where I can adjust things, you know?
I think that makes sense.
That was a good transition though, manually done.
That was good.
I like it.
Okay.
Intentional rage bait will commence in approximately 37 seconds.
Let's double check that gym is activated.
I think it is.
I think it's fine.
Let's see here.
What have I unlocked?
I unlocked something new last time.
What did I unlock?
Samsung with bloodlust.
Let's try it.
Oh, I like the haircut.
That reminds me of Rambo.
Maybe it's related to Rambo.
Oh look, even the little images are of Samson.
I didn't notice that before.
That's cool.
Space item.
Yeah, I know.
Why?
How come they're not supplying the information of Q?
Right here.
I feel like that's essential information.
If you want to tell me about space, why not Q?
Huh?
Weird, isn't it?
Okay, here we go.
We got rock enemies.
I got to take them out.
By the way, I'm just kidding, guys.
I'm not going to intentionally rage bait anything.
If there is any rage bait seeming moments, it's purely me just sucking at the game, okay?
I'm not here.
I'm not out here intentionally making you mad, okay?
I just want to make that clear.
I just suck at the game, all right?
That's okay.
Two bombs to begin with.
That's not bad.
Also, what is my deal here?
Samson.
What does he do?
Why are you special?
Come here, you.
Okay.
Let's look for suspicious rocks.
There's no suspicious rocks.
There's a door, though.
Okay, it's not going to come over here, is it?
Listen, if I destroy that bomb, it's going to destroy the rocks so I can get to the chest.
But I don't have a key so right now that is actually useless.
There's no reason to do it now.
That's called smart gameplay right there.
There's a pill.
I would really love to get in there.
Also, I can do this to get a bomb back.
No, I can't, because that bomb will explode.
So I am going to have to do this, but I will do it down here in case there's a secret room!
Smart!
No, what a horrible start.
One plus one equals anger.
Maybe if you're that actor from that one movie who claims one plus one, it does not equal two.
What is that guy's name?
But it's true.
There's an actor out there who's like enlightened in that way.
It's really funny.
I can't believe that happened.
By the way, I have developed a supervision today.
I will not be able to not dodge projectiles from now on, because I can see everything around me.
Before I saw code, you know, but now I see red dress, green dress, all of that.
You don't do.
Look at that.
Did you see that?
That was pretty much bullet time.
Nice.
One shot, one kill, except it was two shots and one kill.
Beautiful!
The Empress.
We're going to be using that almost immediately.
I have actually evolved to a higher form of being today.
Last fly.
Traces along the edges of walls and obstacles.
And deals contact damage to enemies.
What does that mean?
Traces along the edges of walls and obstacles.
All right.
Draws nearby enemies to target instead of Isaac.
Interesting.
So you do indeed trace along the walls.
They weren't lying.
What about the obstacles though?
I haven't seen them trace that yet.
They were lying to me.
Uh oh.
You can't have this guy throwing bombs.
Wait, how did everything die?
Was that the fly?
Did the fly just kill this down here?
How did that even happen?
That's amazing.
Thanks, fly.
You're the best.
Also, I need keys.
We got a red man over here.
Oh yeah, the fly is actually dealing damage.
Come here.
I see why he's walking along the edges now.
It's to draw the enemies away from me.
It's like that fish, you know, that cleans the tank on its own using its mouth.
I don't know the name of it, but...
Yo!
That was close!
All right, all right.
Not bad.
Thanks, buddy.
I'm gonna look for secrets, of course.
There we go.
I mean, I don't think there's gonna be a secret in here.
In my experience, there has never been a secret in these sort of L-shaped rooms.
Oh, wait a minute, that's not true.
I saw a secret once here.
Watch.
Can we destroy this?
Okay, that didn't work, but sometimes there is a secret there.
I've seen it.
All right, fine.
Maybe here.
Nope.
All right.
The first level is very tiny, though, so that should be expected.
It was a really bad start eating that pill that reduced our HP, but it is what it is.
I still haven't figured out the special ability of Samson here.
I also forgot what it was called.
Something about... yeah, I don't know.
Whoa!
Okay.
Look at me dodging bullets.
Freaking Neo over here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're gonna jump?
Give me a jump.
I know you want to jump.
He looks so happy when he jumps.
Have you noticed?
Look at his face.
Easy mode.
Easy.
Game is easy.
No problem.
What's this?
I feel like I see this matchbook every other run.
Evil up.
So what does that even mean when it says evil up?
It doesn't say that here, though.
It only said it when I was standing next to it.
Plus one black heart spawns three bombs, spawns match stick trinket.
Maybe evil is up because I got a black heart.
Maybe having a black heart means you're evil.
Because only evil people have black hearts, right?
Give me that.
We're moving on.
There's a timer on this one, but we know what?
I don't care.
I have evolved as a human.
Wait, we got minus on damage?
How come that is?
Why is that?
Why did we just get minus on damage?
Maybe it's a general sort of reduction in damage when you go from level to level.
I'm just gonna start assuming shit.
On the basis of nothing.
Better than nothing, I guess, right?
Okay.
These barrels are not gonna be able to destroy any secret walls.
Also, this one has all the doors open, so no secrets here.
Oh yeah.
Beautiful.
No problem.
What is this matchstick do again?
More bombs.
Add additional bombs to chests.
Right, okay.
Speaking of bombs, look at this.
Yahoo!
No problem.
Moving on.
This room.
This guy, I will not get hit once.
He's easy mode.
I'm even gonna bomb him.
Good night, sir!
You get nothing.
In fact, I have a feeling.
Never mind.
The feeling was wrongly adjusted.
Configured.
Today was not the day for that.
What is the best way to deal with these guys?
Maybe a bomb.
You know what?
I'm starting to like using bombs against enemies when I have enough of them.
So the fly is dealing damage, but it's not obvious to me how it happens.
It's almost like it has an aura of damage around it.
Where they just take damage when they're near it.
Get rid of these things.
Oh wait, this guy spawns a little nests, no?
Fly, do you mind helping out with this guy up here?
Come on.
Okay, well that works.
Good.
I have very little damage.
Flawless gameplay.
He's gonna start rushing.
Not dragging, mind you.
Come on.
Look at me shooting!
Holy shit!
I'm a sniper!
Actually insane precision.
The Empress.
Isn't that the same I have?
Yeah, it is.
No problem.
Okay.
Oh, we got jiggly boys!
These are the dangerous ones.
Wait, they're confused by my fly.
Boiled baby.
Why would you boil a baby?
Following familiar that launches scattered bursts of shots at random intervals.
Okay.
I wonder if this fly will also point out secrets to me.
Maybe it'll go like bloop bloop bloop when it's close to a secret wall.
Let's see.
I pulled this straight out of my ass.
I have no idea if there's any basis in that.
This is straight out of the asshole.
No, okay, let me try it.
Nothing.
We're gonna try anymore.
We got three bombs left.
What a night to have a curse!
That's what it said, because I can read at superhuman speed today.
That's right.
Every part of my body and being has been upgraded.
Okay, keep going.
We got poop flies.
Uh-oh.
Getting a little dangerous here.
That works.
Man, the boiled baby is doing work here.
Not even kidding.
This is really good.
And the fly as well!
Incredibile is what they would say in Italy.
We're not in Italy though, so I won't say it.
Big room.
Needs big problems and solutions.
Look at them just soloing everything!
Yo, man, the boiled baby!
Wow, random intervals feels more regular to me, but okay.
Bomb for me.
Let's look for secrets.
Any suspicious stones?
Nothing.
It's clean.
Super clean.
Alright, let's go this way.
They're gonna throw bombs or little thingies.
Projectiles?
We're gonna call them tiles.
The word is too long.
Okay, let's see this room.
There's nothing in here except the boss.
Give me money.
Man, I have found no money yet!
What the actual fuck?
Isn't that kind of crazy?
How dare you cry?
Oh, we got spiders now.
But my fly is doing wonders.
And I think also distracting the enemies.
Isn't that what it said?
Draws nearby enemies to target it, yeah.
So what I really want to do is to stay next to it so that it can draw the enemy fire.
But wait a minute, we have so many bombs.
Nice!
Look at me!
I could smell it, guys.
In my nose.
We got enemy fire?
Not gonna get hit.
Our first coin!
Ah!
I got hit.
Wait, this room is burning.
I've never seen this before.
That's kind of cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're gonna blow this up.
Holy kamali!
That's where all my money went.
Very nice.
I'm gonna blow this up as well.
Oh, everything gets blown up.
Nothing in there.
Wow.
Okay, then we blow this up.
Okay.
More bombs?
That means we're gonna keep bombing.
Ah!
Maybe here?
I want to find everything.
Let's go to the shop since we're now What's this?
Well, that's a new one.
It looks like a toaster.
It's a converter.
Convert your soul.
Okay.
Consumes one soul heart or black heart to grant a red heart container.
Yeah!
That's really good.
That's amazing.
That's probably one of the best actives I've ever had.
I'm gonna kill you.
Nice.
There's still a room up here.
I gotta do that.
Not the spiders.
Spiderino.
El Camino.
Get him.
Come on, baby.
All right.
I'm gonna keep bombing here.
Oh, wait.
Actually, I only have two bombs left.
All right, let's not overdo it.
Back we go.
Rambo is on the path of war.
He seeks no peaceful resolutions.
He wants blood.
And he's gonna get it.
It's Widow.
Bombs for you.
Sog it.
Oh, wow.
Didn't even hit him.
Come here.
Wow.
Okay.
I'm gonna try and predict his movements.
Oh, wait.
I have no more bombs.
I used them all.
That makes sense.
Oh, he's jumping towards the spider.
That's amazing.
Hell yeah.
Okay.
What's this?
Squeezy.
More tears.
And soul hearts!
Dude, we're gonna convert it all to red hearts.
Not bad at all.
And with so many red hearts.
Ooh, give me that.
We're gonna go in here.
Oh, is that... little brimstone.
What?
Following familiar that charges.
Okay, that's good.
Goat head guarantees all devil deals appear and remain open.
But what if I want the opposite of the devil deal?
We're going full out everything.
Give me.
Unfortunately, I can't convert yet, but we will be able to soon.
The toilet dream.
Oh, this is a bad one.
This is one of the bad forebodings.
We lost damage again.
Is it because we gained damage?
In that boss room somehow?
Without realizing it?
This guy down here needs to die.
Come on guys, kill him for me.
Where's that little brimstone?
Okay.
Oh.
If I was quick there, I would have pushed this bomb up here.
But I wasn't quick.
I was slow.
Nice.
He's following the fly.
Come on.
You got him.
Fuck.
This is a good room.
Also, we're gonna do this now.
Space.
Yeah!
The converter!
Ooh, a mushroom.
All stats up!
Whoa!
All right!
Sick!
That's a crazy upgrade.
I do have a bomb left.
I could try and bomb the wall, but I'm not gonna.
I'm saving it until I actually need it.
Thank you, little brimstone!
Let's go in here.
Oh, that's a weird room.
What a horrible night to have a curse.
Oh, they're bombing my fly!
It is so good!
The fly is MVP here.
It's incredible.
Okay.
That's a chain reaction.
Wonderful.
That's my last key.
Ah!
No way!
Insanity!
Very nice.
I wonder what happens to that when I use my converter.
Is it gonna stay on the last, on the second last, on the right, or is it gonna move over?
Let's try it.
As soon as we get enough power.
Spiders?
Oh, I thought that was an enemy.
Good.
Not this guy.
We got brimstone and everything with us though.
With a little brimstone.
Nice!
I have a feeling here.
How fucking good am I?
Jesus Christ!
So good.
You want coins?
I don't think so, buddy.
I'm saving that for the shop.
Also, why is it so dark in here?
Hmm.
I'll be back.
Ah, wait, wait.
We're gonna use this.
Aha!
So, the red heart with the little white piece on it is being moved to the right, unfortunately.
But now we learned that.
Cool.
Let's check the rocks.
Scan, clean.
Green tomatoes!
And that's the boss.
That was beautiful.
Should I go back?
Or not?
I mean, I can't afford the item that I wanted to buy, the compass.
But I can definitely donate to this guy in here and hope for the best.
Maybe I get some keys.
That would actually be fantastic.
Or battery!
Oh, wait.
Are you only gonna get battery?
In that case, no thanks.
I may blow you up.
Cartridge!
Chance to trigger the game kid effect when taking damage.
Ah, but wait a minute.
I kind of like the match stick more.
I thought it was just a passive item that I had.
The match stick is pretty good.
It's giving me a bunch of bombs.
Okay, let's go.
It's the dark one!
Alright.
Wow.
Okay, you're gonna do that.
Oh, it's so dark in here!
I see.
It makes sense.
Ouch!
He destroyed my heart!
Oh, no.
That's too bad.
It is really sad, actually.
I could have had one more.
Hit him!
Now we got him.
No problem.
And a key!
More lock, soul heart, and... Oh, that's good.
I don't want to accidentally step on that, though.
We got the soul heart, so we're gonna do that.
Oh, oh, it was of this?
Mom?
There you are.
A pill.
Not bad.
Dry baby.
We have boiled baby, dry baby, and brimstone baby.
Blocks, enemy shots, chance to deal instant.
Yeah, I like that one.
I've had that the last three runs in a row.
Like, I don't know why am I shooting... why am I shooting three shots at a time here?
Is that related to... what is that related to?
Whoa, this one is even better than I thought.
Damage multiplier, heals all red hearts, more health.
Wow, that is crazy.
What is actually making me shoot like this?
Nothing in my inventory is making me shoot like this.
Huh?
Weird.
Wait, I lost a heart.
Oh wait, I just picked up an item.
It makes sense.
Everything's fine.
Oh, I got a little worried there for a second.
Okay, our goal is to find soul hearts and shit.
With emphasis on shit, I would love to find shit.
Oh, this guy's gonna be trouble, isn't it?
Do I go for it?
Not yet.
We come back later.
Wait, I'm shooting three shots all the time!
That's crazy!
Oh, that was clutch.
Thanks for that.
Why is that happening?
Why am I shooting three?
That's so weird.
You want bombs?
You know what?
It may not be the worst idea.
Check this out.
He's gonna spawn bombs.
I was hoping he would spawn some to the left of me, so I could bounce them into this wall over here.
But...
Okay, what's this?
Tammy says, fires the ring of ten tears.
Ah, no, no, no.
I like this way more.
But we could come back for this when we do have soul hearts.
So, for now, I'm gonna use Tammy's head.
Efficiency, people.
I am so confused why I have this triple shot.
It is beyond anything.
Like, it's crazy.
Fantastic.
That's the boss.
We're not going in there yet, though.
No way.
Man, the diagonal shot is insane.
Being able to just deal with these spiders so easily now is kind of wild.
Get diagonal.
Nerd.
If I could hit you,
I can't hit him at all.
Okay, steam sail.
Sure.
Nice.
Should I use a bomb here?
No, not yet.
I'll look for secrets later.
I need a couple more bombs to justify that.
Also, stones.
Clean.
Now, this room.
This way.
Fantastic.
This one needs two keys!
Ooh, that is a chest room.
And a pill.
Makes you small.
And this is the tower.
That one did troll bombs.
Okay.
That's a troll chest.
Let's do it here.
And hope that it destroys something.
It didn't.
Okay.
Too bad.
Wow.
Close one.
There's just tiles everywhere.
That's right.
We're calling them tiles now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You.
Good.
I still don't understand what Samson's big deal is.
Maybe Samson's big deal is shooting three thingies.
Maybe there's a point where when you reach a certain upgrade threshold, that's when he does it.
Maybe that's Samson.
Or maybe it's just a... what do you call it?
Oh, what's that?
I thought it said pussy worm.
I was like, what?
A pulse worm causes tears to pulse in size.
Do we like that?
I don't think I like that.
No, thanks.
I was about to say, Samson is also a briefcase brand.
No?
Famously, the briefcase that Jim Carrey and Dom and Dumber thought was a name.
When it was actually the brand, right?
Oh, that's a big old bomb.
Did we clear?
Almost.
Let's go check if that door is open now.
That's still one of the Is how to consistently get into these rooms here.
That room.
Maybe it means I need to kill everything that exists.
Wait, let me actually try.
We haven't gone in here yet.
This guy wants hearts.
I don't think I like that.
I will not give you my hearts.
No.
Time for the boss.
I could give you bombs.
No, no, bad idea.
Go!
The hollow!
That was amazing.
All right then!
Boom, shaka, laka, laka.
We have eavesdrops, eyedrops.
More tears, increases fire rate.
Ooh, yes.
Keep crying.
Okay, we're gonna go in here.
What's this?
We don't know.
This one is more damage.
Oh, that is a good one, though.
That is a good one.
I feel like I want to take both.
We're going crazy.
Oh, this is a... it's an active.
Oh, shit.
Maybe all books are active, actually.
Deals instant damage to all enemies in the room.
All right.
I don't want it, though, unfortunately, because I have a date with another item that I'm gonna go get now.
A very important item.
Yeah, I would love to keep this, but, you know, it is what it is.
I need this thing.
Best active in the game, so far.
I will say the Shoop-da-boop is also up there.
And, of course, Las Biplos was also quite good.
Right, let's go.
We have arrived in the oven, it seems.
That's what that icon reminds me of.
It's the depths.
Okay.
We lost a lot of damage.
Fantastic.
Ooh, that hurt.
That hurt.
Okay.
They're gonna keep jumping, aren't they?
Just keep moving.
Okay.
What's that?
Apple of Sodom.
50% chance to convert a red heart into blue spiders instead of healing.
100% chance of it full health.
Ooh.
Trig- oh, that actually sounds pretty good.
We also have this thing here, but I may not pick it up until the very end.
Wait, if I use my converter on this, that's not gonna work, right?
Because it's only on black hearts or soul hearts.
Got it.
That's okay.
Oh, not this guy.
We're gonna blow him up.
I'm actually kind of in the danger zone here.
Shoot the barrels.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
Having all these projectiles kind of helps against this guy.
He's less annoying because of that.
I have a feeling right here.
Watch my feeling.
Okay, right here.
Damn!
My feeling is never wrong.
How does that happen?
I don't understand.
Beautiful.
That's needed.
Just honestly played safe from a distance.
Mom!
One of them is camouflage!
I see you there, buddy!
Okay.
Not too shabby.
Where's my soul heart set, though?
Oh, what a weird room.
No enemies.
A big room with no enemies?
That's rare, isn't it?
Ah, we lost the special heart.
That's to be expected, honestly.
I would be surprised if we kept it.
One makes you larger.
Oh, I'm very large now.
Maybe too large.
This could be a big problem.
You want bombs?
No.
Yes!
Massive.
Much needed.
Let's check the rocks.
Clean.
Uh-oh, we have a classic four-dimensional issue here.
But we have keys.
That's fine.
Aha!
There we go!
Convert!
Immediate conversion.
Kill him.
Uh-oh.
Jim!
Help me, Jim!
Nice.
Jim was there to help me.
Nightlight creates a cone of light.
Oh, that one is actually pretty good.
Oh, we gotta take this.
We gotta take that.
We gotta take this.
Actually, we didn't gotta take that, but I took it.
I wanted to took it.
Uh, let's donate.
Okay.
Come at me, bro.
My nightlight shines on you.
Beautiful.
This is the best active in the game.
Changed my mind.
It's insanity.
Uh, there's a couple rooms we missed.
This way.
I wish I could get another pill that makes me smaller.
Oh, not that way.
I am way too big.
What does this happen?
Oh, we picked up a heart, right?
And we gained spiders.
That is what is happening.
Okay these guys are not too big of an issue.
What?
Oh, okay.
I was about to say.
Dude, I look stylish as hell.
This is where it's at right here.
Scan the stones.
Clean.
But, I sense.
I didn't sense correctly.
What's up dudes?
Man, this guy wants hearts.
Bad trip?
No!
Wait, we gain damage?
So maybe bad trip is good?
Oh, interesting.
Why do we just gain damage?
That's still closed, unfortunately.
Okay, let's do... we grab the heart and then we keep going.
Down this way.
Fill me up.
Wait.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, shit!
I thought it was only at a hundred health.
Damn.
Well, in that case, I may not like this at all.
We're gonna change it out.
Fuck this item.
It sucks.
Where's my other item?
I think it's up here.
Somewhere.
Yeah, that was actually horrible.
We don't like that at all.
This item sucks.
Good item revoked status.
You were good until you weren't.
At least I'm gonna get some bombs now.
You know what?
Let's look for secrets.
Could there be a secret in here?
Maybe here.
Aha!
Oh, I don't want to hang myself.
Yet.
We all float down here.
Huh?
Oh!
Yeah!
That's... I would love to hang myself.
Please!
Hand me the rope.
Again?
Oh, leads back to where I was.
Got it.
All right.
Moving on.
Ah, this way.
Here.
Was there anything else I wanted to do here?
Maybe kill that guy?
Hey!
Donate.
There you go.
166.
We just need a 500 or so more.
And then we're at the right point.
Okay, what do we got?
We got not much.
Loki.
Wait, does he have 666 on his forehead?
I just noticed that.
Well, there you go.
We got a box.
Oh, all kinds of good stuff here.
Aha!
Convert!
What's that?
Flat worm.
Tears are 50% wider.
Tears have slightly more knockback.
Whoa!
Oh, that's pretty damn good.
The hanged... Oh, the hanged man!
Grant's flight.
That's funny.
What a coincidence.
We also got a... No, absolutely not.
Health down.
Come on now.
I'm not going to do that.
All right, let's... Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Holy shit!
We don't know what that is.
Generate the trail of damage and creep, and we have... Let me grab that, I guess.
I think I'm going to take this.
Evil up.
Your enemies will pay.
Ooh, that sounds cool.
Blackheart?
Deals room-wide damage upon taking a hit that reduces Isaac to one heart remaining.
Okay.
Unfortunately, they can't do a convert.
Yes, we can!
You ready for the ultimate play?
The ultimate play is backtracking.
That's right.
We're going to convert.
You'll see.
Evolved life form in front of your eyes.
Wait, we don't even need to pay.
We can just go.
Yikes!
Convert!
And we're going to grab another one.
Unless we're flying.
Oh, hell yeah.
Easy peasy.
Lemon squeezy.
No lemon mishap, though.
Only the squeezy.
No secret stones, unfortunately?
That's kind of sad.
Moving on.
I think I see them now.
They're definitely arms.
I can see the... I see how it works now.
I see clearly now.
They're not fucking breastfeeding.
Wait, they never were, but you know what I mean.
I saw it clear.
Nice.
Kill this heart.
Very good.
Let's go up here.
There's even a dick spot here, guys.
If we find a shovel, we keep it in mind.
This guy's spawning tomatoes out of his poop hole.
What is this?
Fantastic!
Heck yeah!
Oh man, the way... that looks like some balls.
Look at my balls just vibrating there.
Doesn't it?
Call me crazy.
Look at it.
Those are what we in Danish call Klonka.
Clear as day.
I think it's intentional as well.
This game likes to play with all the body parts, you know?
Bombs.
And look at this over here.
What's that?
Number one.
Haha!
I see.
It's P. We got tears, but less range.
Ooh, a lot of less range.
Tears turn yellow and fire from lower.
Hahaha!
That's amazing.
Okay, that range is atrocious.
But wait a minute!
Ah, okay, I was about to say it's only my straight thing that shoots less, but it's actually all directions.
That's fine.
I can't really express myself right now, apparently.
What's this all about?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, this is not good.
That could have been done better, I admit it.
Boy, the P is effective.
Uh oh.
But did it grant me something good in return?
Health down?
What is it with these pills?
Stop it.
I don't want that.
Ah, should I go in here?
No, not yet.
I'm saving it.
I'm keeping an eye out for suspicious rocks as well.
I'm not seeing any yet.
I do see suspicious poop.
I can't even reach it.
I missed a heart in there.
That's okay.
Huh?
Why is the poop not being destroyed?
Oh wait, I can fly.
I'm an idiot.
Oh my god!
I forgot I could fly.
Right.
Oh yeah.
I gotta get used to that.
It's okay, I saw it though.
I was just testing you guys.
Everything is fine.
Intentional is what that was.
Kill them all.
Wrap that.
There's another dick spot here.
That's right, I see them all.
Nice.
Yo, what happens if you get a half a blue heart?
What happens then?
Oh wait, I can fly.
I'm an idiot.
I need to get used to that.
So I have half a heart now.
Let me convert.
Doesn't work.
Okay, you need a full one.
Full one is needed.
Gotcha.
Actually kind of pertinent information.
Another dick spot there?
I saw it.
Let me actually do this.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
Come on.
Nice.
That was beautiful.
Nailed that one.
We got ten monies.
Mom's bottle of pills.
Oh, it's discounted because we have steam sale.
Oh, I love generating a lot of pills though.
What makes you small?
Huge!
I mean, small.
But you know what I mean.
That's the Hank, man.
We don't care about that.
This is an unknown.
The higher effect.
I know what that does.
It's a good one.
It gives me range, I think.
I think that's what it does.
Got a heart here, but we don't need that.
Nope, we don't need it.
Converter.
Yeah, we're gonna leave that here until later.
You also missed the bomb in here, it seems.
Got it.
Okay, moving on.
Oh, but I can fly.
Oh, but I can't shoot while inside of here.
Okay,
we got that.
Any suspicious rocks?
Not that I can see.
Are they gonna activate?
Yeah, they are.
Bastards.
How can I get that?
Wow, that's a tough one to get.
Without taking damage, that is.
Easy.
Boss time?
We are missing a room.
And I would love to get a couple more pills until we fight the boss.
God, our character is disgusting.
It's like a little demon baby.
Okay, demon fire gone.
Wait, how did they die?
They sort of just died.
Oh, it's the fly!
Not bad at all.
Petrified poop!
Chance for destroyed poop to spawn a pickup.
I mean, we could use that.
Yeah, why not?
For a bit.
And then we change back.
Yeah, I like that.
Whoa!
That's a lot of chests.
Heralysis, freezes Isaac and plays for two seconds.
But, what else does it do?
Maybe nothing else.
I was trying to see if my stats were changing.
Laos!
Small chance of spawning a blue spider any time Isaac is in a room with enemies.
Spawns a blue spider on room clear.
Nah, I'm not a big fan of the spiders.
What did I just get?
Oh, the higher fed!
It's too so large!
What the fuck?
We need that.
Ah, that's too bad.
But it's okay, we go convert now.
Give me that.
Convert, convert, convert where they'll leave it.
I think I left it down in that room down here.
Yeah, I could be wrong.
No, it's here.
Beautiful.
And the pills.
I think I'm gonna bring the converter with me.
And then maybe take this one, except it doesn't really do anything.
Blow him up.
Spawn spiders.
Alright, whatever.
Maybe the Hankman card will do something special.
Just like the Bible did something special, you know?
Maybe all of these items have some weird use case.
We're gonna try here.
The Hankman.
Yes, yes, what is it?
Sounds like I'm taking damage, but I'm really not.
Where's the foot?
I keep watching for the shadow!
There's no foot!
What the hell?
Blue cap.
Tears, less shot speed.
Health!
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Very good.
Oh, we don't need that one.
What's that?
Oh, they're both new!
We gotta take them both.
Too spooky for me.
More shot speed and tears.
Yeah, applies fear to enemies in close range of Isaac.
Wow.
Guppy's paw.
Soul converter?
Hold on!
Permanently removes 1 HP to grant 3 soul hearts.
Haha!
Guys!
We use this!
And we convert!
Oh, we don't have mana, but... Right?
Hello?
That's crazy!
Well, let's go!
Okay, it's the womb.
Shoot the shit out of everyone.
I'm looking for... Oh, this rock looks a little differently colored, doesn't it?
No?
Hmm.
Maybe they do need to have the eggs on it.
Pretty much every one of them has one.
Huge!
Nice.
This way.
What the hell is that?
Wait, is that a wormhole?
Oh, I can't fall in.
Okay.
Ha!
Oh, they are trapped.
The poop was holding them together.
Go in here.
Blow that up.
Still no idea what that does.
I guess it's good.
Convert.
Like it must be good, right?
Oh, that's a friend.
Where are you going?
Are we done in here?
Oh, you!
I didn't even see you.
Okay.
A charge.
Nice.
Oh, I got a big guy.
Oh, he got scared because he got close to me!
There's not a guaranteed thing or... Maybe there's an internal cooldown on it.
Get rid of that guy.
Convert!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, there's poop!
Eliminated.
Aha!
Easy.
Oh my god!
The conversion!
It's gonna happen.
Wait, what is this weird room?
There's gotta be something here.
I got three bombs left.
I should probably save them.
If something looks super obvious, then I'm gonna go for it.
Money.
Do we got anything suspicious in here?
I don't think so.
Nice.
That's the boss.
Not yet, though.
Convert!
Keep going.
This is the best active item in the game.
It's not even close!
It is on a whole other level.
Compare that to the key one.
Makes me wanna puke!
Convert!
That was a bomb.
Oh, we can go in there.
Why is that?
Let's think.
Why is this open?
Why is that open?
What have I done?
Maybe you need a minimum amount of hearts to enter.
You need to be healthy enough to go in there, or maybe you need a minimum of damage.
Could be that you need a hundred percent demon mode.
Could also be that you have not defeated the boss yet, or something else.
I'm not sure.
There could be many reasons.
Oh, there's a guy down there.
Oh, this is gonna be so good against these guys having three shots.
Oh, hell yeah, dude.
Where are you?
There you are.
Come out.
Okay.
I'm taking that.
I know it was a little bit wasteful, but whatever.
Get slowed.
Convert!
Bombs.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go out.
Let me go left up here.
Oh, yeah.
I have a feeling.
Man, my feelings are not on point right now.
Okay, this one, for sure.
What?
Okay, fine.
Boss time.
This is not the heart yet.
This is the one before the heart.
Oh, actually, you know what?
Let's go in here.
Pills!
Whoo!
Nice!
Except it didn't do anything.
Wow.
Full health?
Yo, we're gonna save that.
Look how I brought it to the fucking chest!
It was half accident, half intentional, okay?
It's not like I intended it immediately.
I will admit that, okay?
It was not that smart.
Going in.
Mama Gertie!
That's a disgusting hand!
Holy shit, dude.
Shooting three times projectiles against this guy?
Alrighty!
Supper!
Even more red hearts.
I like it.
And we can go in here.
I can take these deals all day.
Ouija board.
Spectral tears and tears up.
You love to see it.
Oh, it didn't say tears up on the description here, isn't that weird?
Why is that?
And this one, little horn.
Cants to fire void tears that summon Bighorn's hand to attack enemy struck.
Chance increases with luck.
Okay, we're at zero, though.
Bighorn's hand instantly kills normal monsters and deals heavy damage to bosses.
Also causes Isaac to deal a small amount of contact damage to enemies.
I mean, we take it.
We take it.
It's simple.
We take those.
Do we just go?
I guess we do.
I think it's about time we switch out the converter now for something else.
experimental treatment has appeared fighting baby she'll curse of darkness oh good thing I have a flashlight a not bad at all you want money huh good thing I have money I'll give you all my money does this mean beggars end up in hell or This is kind of dark symbolism.
This is definitely hell.
Thanks.
Yeah, nice.
How about some bombs?
That's what I really need right now.
What's that?
Butterbean.
I think I've had it before.
At least a fart that pushes away nearby enemies and reflects nearby.
Okay, yeah.
That's actually pretty good.
I mean, anything is better than the converter now.
The converter is useless now.
Whoa!
Demon versions of the Brainiac thingies.
Give me that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
The secret is also revealed here!
There's two!
And why are they so big?
Looks like they encompass four rooms.
Whoa!
Crazy.
What about this blue fire, huh?
What are you guys even doing?
You're burning.
Burning a lot.
Oh wait, I missed a bomb back there!
I saw it.
So since my tears are spectral, I think I can just shoot through these guys.
And they should be able to take damage, even though I hit them from the front, right?
Just like the laser.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Spiders too.
Watch this down here.
How am I taking damage?
Oh, it's the rock.
I think I went into the rock.
Teleport to the Devil or Angel Room.
Wow!
A secret room.
Where do I want to go first?
Let's go to this one.
I didn't mean to poop.
Oh, uh-oh.
What the hell?
Shopkeeper!
Good night, sir.
Thanks for playing.
All right, so I can go two ways.
Dude, the music here is pretty damn scary.
Makes me think that I'm gonna get fucked any moment, you know?
Flashlight is actually amazing.
Release thy form!
Come on, dude.
Like, I hate these guys.
It's insane.
Every variation of these guys are the
worst secret room, by the way.
Massive.
I love when that triggers.
Let's look at these rocks.
I've looked at the rocks.
Load up.
Aha!
Does that work to give me one extra heart?
Or is it useless?
I guess we'll find out.
Maybe this is the only way to gain even more hearts.
There's the boss.
So is that gonna be Satan?
Or what?
Hold on, we gotta explore everything.
I want to go deeper!
I want to fight this guy!
I want to go deeper, deeper!
If we even can!
This may be the end, actually.
Anything else in here?
No.
This eye cannot be killed.
Okay, but it can't be killed by the hand.
Cool.
Thanks.
Butterbean!
Get beaned on, nerds.
I mean, that's useless to me.
Oh wait, now I can sit inside the rocks and shoot!
Because I've got the spectral tears.
That was the limitation I ran into before, but now it's fine.
Okay, I'm gonna try and bomb here.
Oh wait, we know what the secrets are, so there's no reason.
That was dumb.
Wow.
Thank you.
Oh, not these guys.
Okay, we killed one of them.
Got him.
Butterbean!
Wait, that damaged him or what?
I think it may have damaged him.
There's one more room I want to go to.
Let's see what's in this one.
Copies the effective I6 active item.
Oh, that's what?
The Butterbean?
What does it actually do?
I need to see this.
Well, this is a fart that pushes away nearby enemies and reflects nearby.
Okay, okay, okay, I need to remember that.
Reflects projectile.
That's kind of huge.
I gained extra damage just now!
By going through and taking damage from those doors?
That gives me damage.
Well, we can't go deeper, it seems, unfortunately.
So we're gonna have to fight this guy, and I think it's gonna be tough, because I honestly don't even remember what he does.
Look at that stuff on the floor here.
Evil markings.
There was also a red axe down here, in case we had a shovel.
So maybe there is something to be found there.
Okay, let's do this.
Here we go.
Satan!
Bombs!
Oh wait, that's not Satan?
Oh, it is Satan, okay.
Oh, my fart doesn't work against his lasers, apparently.
Wow!
Bombs for you!
I'm just gonna hide over here, if you don't mind.
Did we do it?
We're not done yet.
Oh, man, I don't know what's happening!
Deal damage!
Kill him before he kills us!
Yeah!
Sick!
Now, wait a minute.
Can we go further down somehow?
Is it possible?
Let me think.
What else can I do?
I kind of don't want to go into the chest!
Is that crazy?
Wait, there's also this.
I wish I had a shovel.
Okay.
What if I bomb it?
Hold on.
Oh, I don't have any bombs.
Here we go.
Is that the same we had last time?
Okay, that one was the same.
Pretty good.
Bloodwrights has appeared.
Okay.
Oh, look at that!
Two parts of four!
It's a freaking map!
Interesting!
All right, we're gonna go again.
Also, I need to see something real quick.
Samson, bloodlust.
What does that even mean?
I have no idea what that did.
My theory is that it produced the three-shot thingies.
Because I shot three shots at one point and my items didn't do it, so I don't know.
Eve, Judas... Oh, that's also new!
Book of Belial.
Let's try that.
One heart, two speed, four attack!
Where are you?
In the basement.
Okay.
He has one of those funny hats on that the religious people have.
Oh, wait, we have a book!
Is that the Book of Belial?
It is!
Gain damage up for the current room, passively increases Devil Angel room chance.
Okay.
Got it.
Let's try.
Plus four damage!
Oh, that's a lot.
Oh, wait, we have one!
We have only one heart.
We gotta be really careful there.
Wow.
I forgot about that part.
I was too excited about the damage.
Uh-oh.
It's over.
Well, there we go!
Let's try that again, huh?
Okay, Curse of the Lost.
That means we can't see the map.
Man, how do you even dodge that?
There's too many enemies.
Okay, that's better.
Man, having one HP to start with is really rough.
This Book of Belial better be good.
Okay, no suspicious rocks.
Looks like we have decent damage.
Yeah, damage is good.
Can't complain about...
It's like a glass cannon.
It's not the squiggly, boys.
That's good at least.
Oh my god, we're getting rich.
Give me damage.
Come on, nice.
The tower?
It's a bunch of bombs.
Eyesore.
Each tier has a chance to fire additional shots.
Okay, it's a pretty good one.
I'm gonna keep doing this.
Wait, is it gonna spawn a new one?
I have to try.
Doesn't look like it.
And now we can find a shop.
That's fine.
Actually, I'm gonna destroy this.
I had to test whether or not we could just, you know, if we had the money, go for infinite items.
We got pills, but no bombs.
I'm so ripped.
Oh, I could have used it if I was smart.
I'm fast, but I'm neither.
All right, I don't want to go in there.
That's death sentence on this character.
No, thanks.
Wait a minute.
That's where we started.
Aha!
That was kind of a crazy shot just now.
I'm proud of myself.
Right, the map doesn't work.
No, thanks.
So where do I actually go?
I must have missed something in this direction.
What about over here?
Wait a minute.
Oh, there's a door here.
Aha!
He's camouflaged.
He likes to poop.
Why can't I... Why was there no, like, little pop-up?
I can't.
Is that the curse?
Like, even if I press shift, I can't get the highlight to come up.
Or the tooltip.
The tower is the one that spawns troll bombs, and this one takes me back to the first room.
Let's take this one.
Hey guys, you like this?
Uh-oh, I was in the corner.
Not good.
Okay.
Uh-oh.
The boss with half an HP?
That's very... Oh, never mind.
We got saved by the gods above.
Alright, here we go.
Damage!
It's Poopy Boi.
Bokeh Belial will fuck you up.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Okay, okay, okay.
You've got no chill.
I see, I see.
Calm down now.
A red shoe.
Range up.
That's a significant amount of extra range.
I like it.
Uh, no special room, unfortunately.
Too bad.
Uh, yeah, I think we did everything on this floor, because I couldn't find my way.
Which means I explored everything, clearly.
Nice.
Milk.
Almond milk.
Ooh, that's a lot of extra tears, but... Whoa, hold on.
You know what?
I say no to that.
I think I say no to that.
Minus 3.31 tears?
That's gonna leave me with what?
Ooh, 6.9, uh... 3.69, 2.69-ish.
No, 1.69.
It's horrible, is what I'm saying.
I can't do math.
Give me coins, though.
Oh, oh, okay.
I'll come back here for that later.
Maybe I'll take it later.
If I find some more damage, then I'll consider it.
Jiggly boys!
Wait, something just happened.
He attacked me and I gained something.
Why is that?
Oh, it was minor contact damage.
Ah, I see.
But I didn't lose any HP.
So when it happens, I don't lose HP.
That's crazy.
Very good.
Man, you need to stop puking that shit.
There we go.
Now we go this way.
Damage is good.
Kill that guy.
Nice.
Keys and bombs, we got everything.
May not have been worth it.
It felt good in the moment.
Uh-oh.
I'm in trouble here.
How did everything die?
I don't get that part.
Teleport to the starting room.
I'm low HP here.
This is getting very risky.
I gotta go back and grab that half a heart.
Just to play it safe.
We gotta find, like, HP upgrade here.
Otherwise, it's gonna be a very short one.
What did that shoe do again?
Oh, it had contact damage and range.
Cheers.
Bring it on!
Oh!
Fucking corners!
That was not good.
In fact, it was pretty bad.
This one should be manageable, though.
Give me some good stuff in that poop.
Nothing.
I can't even afford anything in here.
How come I can't see?
Oh, now they pop up.
Okay.
I can buy this one.
Is it worth it?
Oh, actually really good.
Kind of a waste, though, right?
Oh, this one is better right now.
Shit.
Get away.
No way!
That is amazing.
I'm gonna grab that.
Actually, take this for now.
And you want keys?
That's exactly what I have!
No way!
Awesome!
Thanks.
More.
Okay, that's all you're gonna get.
I'm not gonna blow you up.
You've been a good one.
I'll save this.
Oh, they're fast.
They caught me off!
Crazy.
I can get to that.
Ah, damn.
I really thought I could.
We gotta go in.
Larry Jr.
Should be okay, I think.
I hope.
Yeah, there we go.
The belts, get some speed.
No special rooms for me, though.
Unfortunately.
You know what?
I'm gonna go back.
Oh, that was close.
I'm actually gonna pick up that item.
Because I feel like if it's an item that drops, you know, and it's gotta be good.
And it is a lot of attack speed.
I will say that.
So if I do find damage later, it's gonna be pretty good, right?
Yeah, let's just take it.
Like, that is...
Okay.
Why are they so small, though?
It didn't say anything about that.
Greatly decreases tier damage.
Each tier gains a random worm effect.
Okay, but why are they so small?
There was no mention of that.
I feel like I've been lied to once again.
The game is not truthful.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, look at this rock right here.
Hold on.
I see a bomb.
Potential.
Wait, what?
Up here?
Five co... Oh, I can't buy it, though.
Maybe, maybe, maybe...
Give me a bomb.
Bomb me!
A pill?
Please be good.
Alright!
Alright, I guess that was okay.
Moving on.
Too bad I wanted to bomb that thing real bad.
It's okay.
Okay, we still gotta find more health, because 1 HP is no fun.
It's gonna give me an early grave, 100%.
This is ridiculous.
Absolutely ridiculous.
I will not be able to see what is belonging to me or not.
It's a lighter.
A chance to inflict burn on an enemy when entering a new room.
Increases with luck.
Alright.
Sounds good.
Burn!
My friend.
I need you to burn.
Kill all the small ones first.
This is how we do it.
Alright, this is just crazy.
Imagine I get more damage now.
I need more damage.
This is absolutely wild.
What's happening?
No, no, not the worms!
Man, they have a lot of HP.
Or I should say I have very little damage.
Got him.
There's more.
Come on, man.
There we go.
I go this way.
Uh-oh.
Oh, I got almost caught there.
It was close.
Man, my damage is bad.
I really regret picking that up, actually.
Oh, this is a good card.
I like that.
We're going to use that against the boss.
How do I get to that one?
I see the rock situation.
We can definitely get to the coin if I had a bomb.
But not the heart.
Okay.
That went better than expected.
Like this active right now.
Actually, my active plus the card is going to do crazy damage.
Because of the attack speed, right?
Let's kill this guy first.
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good.
No keys!
Too bad.
Let's go in here.
You're not going to hit me.
Oh, I need a key real bad to get into that room.
I need to get in there.
Oh, my God.
Ah, you bastard!
Can't believe you hit me.
I'm going back for health.
Still no key.
It should be doable.
You're not going to come up here?
Okay, now you are.
I double the area.
Come on.
That works.
Let's go north.
I need to do this.
Wow.
No keys, no bombs, huh?
It's going to be like that.
Holy fucking guacamole!
Kill him!
Insanity.
This door opened!
Ooh, wait.
I got to do it.
Eternal life, oh.
Ex-lax.
Yeah, come to me, bitches.
I got lemons.
Lemons for y'all.
You like that?
You like lemons?
Oh no, the lemon disappeared.
That's too bad.
What's this?
I could activate that.
All right, all right, all right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, come on.
God, this damage is atrocious.
Oof, I need more HP.
Man, oh man.
But I found something else.
Let me see what I found.
Gobbish collar!
Okay, okay, that's pretty good.
But only maybe.
Only maybe good.
Well, we could not find a key which is actually freakin' unbelievable.
So, rip.
I'm gonna keep my strength instead.
Yeah.
And then go this way.
Time for the boss.
Wish me luck.
I'm going... let me see, mega fatty.
Definitely doing this one.
You're gonna puke, right?
That's your thing.
Yeah, here it comes.
Dodge, dodge, dodge, dodge.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very nice, very nice.
We got a bar of soap!
Tears and more shot speed.
Okay, but what about damage, man?
I need damage!
Also, we can't go in here.
I mean, we can go in here, but we can't do anything.
I guess I can open the box.
Hey, there we go!
But I...
Wait, that's gonna consume my red heart if I do, though, right?
Hold on.
Yeah, I can't do this.
This would be game over if I did.
Shit!
Man, I am fighting for my life in this run, at every single second.
It's dark as well, and I got no flashlights.
Oh, no, not this room.
This is hell itself.
Wait, I have an idea.
I'm gonna wait for the spikes.
Fuck me!
Nice!
This is one of the hardest rooms.
Well, I have no damage, man.
What's that?
Familiars follow more closely?
Damage follow?
I mean, sure, why not.
Then again, I think I like this more, because I have no familiars.
I could go into the challenge room.
Arcade?
No, we save it for something better.
Let's do it.
Yes!
Massive!
Come on, then.
Huh?
I don't even know how I just died.
What did I die from?
Uh-oh.
Well, I got the item.
I'm not going back in.
I got it.
I got the Jesus Juice.
We keep going.
That's healing?
No!
Wow, this is not good, guys.
It's pretty much over.
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Brother man!
Stay away from me!
Holy shit!
Haha!
Belial me!
Belial!
Kill him!
Kill him all!
Oh my goodness, I need that.
This is such a waste, but I have to.
I gotta do it.
No!
They're gonna shoot!
Fuck!
Holy shit!
Enemies!
No enemies.
But I can't get over there.
Oh, that's such a tease.
What a tease.
I gotta do this.
Damage.
Yeah, I'm too scared.
This could kill me.
Range up.
It...
It
doesn't get more unlucky than this!
It's insane!
Wow!
Ah, man!
Man, oh, man!
Kill him all!
Mega battery!
Sick!
Boss time?
Man, we gotta find...
Ah, man.
Where's my item room?
That's what I need.
Probably down here.
Uh-oh.
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi!
Mamma mia!
Holy shit, we found it.
Birds eye?
It burns?
I don't like that.
I thought it was a chili!
I was hoping it gave me HP.
That's when firing tears to also fire a sliding red flame projectile.
Which deals heavy contact damage.
Okay.
All right, man, it's not looking good.
Let's go to the arcade, man, and start gambling.
That's what I want to do.
That's a great fucking idea.
Yes, this way.
I mean, that's...
Let's do this guy.
Both.
Battery, okay.
Come on, man.
Oh, what?
Give me something good.
Very unlucky.
Once.
Oh, okay.
I mean, I'm gonna use those to kill you.
You know that, right?
That was a mistake on your part.
Nice!
There we go.
And goodbye.
Yeah.
We kill them all.
Oh, massive.
Thanks.
You know what?
Let's go find some more HP.
I believe.
I'm too scared.
I saw scary enemies and I had to click the button.
We do have extra mana, right?
That's okay.
It's the swiggly, swiggly bus!
Oh, that's always such a scary thing.
Wait, could be HP in there.
There's money.
Nice.
Oh, okay.
I thought that flame came for me.
Okay.
What about the challenge room thingy?
Wait, wasn't this open to begin with?
That was open when we came here and now it's closed.
I think.
Could be wrong.
Let's not assume.
Going to boss.
Unfortunately, oh, wait a minute.
Ah, no.
Never mind.
Here we go!
Carrion Queen.
I've never seen that.
What about that little heart?
That's probably bad.
We got to kill it, right?
Kill the little heart.
We're producing a lot of flames.
Good.
Wait, I wonder if he takes damage when he walks on the flames that are currently on the floor.
Or if it's only when they move.
More damage and more range.
What about HP?
I am just destined to be at one HP, huh?
Okay.
At least we got some extra damage.
That was sorely needed.
Okay.
Depth one.
Uh-oh.
Oh, it's fucking over.
Oh, man!
I thought it was over for sure.
I really did.
What the hell is this room?
Hahaha!
It can't even move!
That's too bad, guys.
I need that money.
Gracias.
Bro, I don't know what's happening on my screen.
There's too much crap.
All right.
We are in deep shit here.
What did I die from?
Was it the fucking stuff on the floor?
Motherfucker.
It's impossible to see that bullshit.
What's this?
Tiny planet?
What?
Insane range?
Spectral tears?
Tears fire in a circle around Isaac?
I hate that!
That is frickin' horrible!
Oh, no!
No!
Yikes!
Bro, that is just the worst!
Even if it gave me 10 extra damage, I'm not even sure it would be worth it.
I kinda wanna just die and start over.
This is horrible!
It is absolutely horrible.
Wow.
I mean, I'm probably gonna die anyway, because it is horrible, so...
I will get my wish soon enough.
It's like playing I.O.
from Dota.
That's what this is.
Thanks.
I may as well just keep one direction going.
Go down here.
I'm doing my best with what I got here.
This door can be opened with two bombs.
I don't possess two bombs.
I also need a bomb here.
I need three bombs in total.
It's a little bit better now.
I'm getting used to it a little bit more.
Please tell me I can open this door.
Okay, good.
Fantastic!
About time.
Hey, more health!
About time!
That's what I've been wanting.
The entirety of Last Run.
Very good.
Secret room, baby!
I guess it's good for situations like this, where I can hide behind rocks.
Let's just go to the secret room.
Oh, it was here.
All right.
I wonder if there is like a systematic way to...
kind of predict where it's going to be.
Because it feels super random.
Holy shit, that was close.
Oh, look at this!
Ah!
It even works in here!
But I can't really do much there, that's funny.
Ghost baby.
Fire spectral tears, got it.
Okay.
That's pretty cool, I guess.
Keep moving.
Oh, you're stuck in there, are you?
Are you stuck?
Step?
Isix?
Or whatever?
I look like Isix, don't I?
Nice.
This is the troll bombs.
You know what?
Fuck it, let's go.
I'm going to troll the shit out of Gemini, you'll see.
Unbelievable.
Okay, there we go, there we go.
That's something.
Wait, something from the future.
Is what we unlocked.
Holy monies.
Flat penny.
Wait a minute, why are there two...
It was a fake boss!
Hold on a minute, before I go in there.
I've got to heal up.
I can't believe that.
There's another heart.
Definitely grabbing that.
Could be the difference between... Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay, never mind.
Thought I saw something.
No bomb still!
It's actually crazy.
Yeah, I'm not going to go into that room where I lose HP.
I like my outfit here.
I got a crown on one side and a religious hat on the other.
Is it the Jews that wear this one for Bar Mitzvah or something?
Or is it the one in the East?
I actually forgot which one.
But I do recognize this hat.
It's a religious hat.
Okay, now we go in here.
Dingle!
We're going to use the book of Belial.
Oh, you came a third time.
Dodge that.
I'm ready for you.
I'm not ready.
I take it back.
Okay, it works.
More damage and more range.
No, man, where's all my good rooms at?
My item rooms.
Devil rooms.
Ah, look, speaking of devil, a hundred percent devil now.
Let's try and pay attention to if it stays at a hundred.
What's up, nerd?
You can't handle my planets.
Give me that.
Uh-oh.
This is so frickin' hard.
Oh, man.
Oh, yep.
Nice.
Oh, okay.
Whoo!
Oh, we lost devil!
What happened?
Maybe I can't go in here.
So, I went in here.
I killed this guy.
I went in here.
What happened?
I lost HP?
Maybe?
I didn't do it perfectly?
Is that it?
Fuck!
I was stuck in a corner.
It's this guy again.
Like, I can't win.
Okay, that's better.
Oh, I gotta start using my book.
This is not worth it for this book in here, but...
Like, I'm stuck in a corner.
I can't do anything.
Sometimes it's like you're just fucked by the geometry of the level and the spawns of the enemies.
Minidooka flies.
Okay, I've got a bomb, though.
That's some... Oh, oh, I got a bomb.
I got a bomb!
Why was it moving?
Fuck this bullshit.
I swear to God, man.
That feels horrible.
I need a shop.
Look at all my money.
I couldn't even see the projectile that I got hit by.
I could not even see it at all.
And I was looking, you know?
Shit is rough, man.
Man, this is a hard-ass character to play.
This is one of the harder ones.
Oh, we go down here.
I get the same items.
Like, there's apparently, like, so many items in this game.
How come I get the same items again and again and again?
How about some new ones?
Am I just being supremely unlucky here, or what?
It's insanity.
How about some new ones?
Cough them up, man.
I know you got them.
Fuck you.
Come here.
There we go.
No healing, though, so we gotta do this.
Gotta pray to the evil gods below.
That extra damage is really nice.
Huge.
Wait, this is the exact same room I just had.
Look at this.
Isn't that kind of crazy?
Wow.
You know what?
Why not?
Famine.
So what else do you do, famine?
Oh, okay, you do the charge.
Shoot some balls at me.
I see your stance.
More balls coming?
No, not yet.
Oh, no.
Okay, well, that was that.
Man, I don't think I can ever win with this character.
It is insanely difficult with 1 HP.
Like, you gotta play perfect.
It is a rough one.
Even that fire right now could ruin my whole career, if I wasn't careful, you know?
I'm not sure the trade-off of having less HP, but then also having only one heart.
Sorry, having less HP and then having more damage is worth it.
Like, the damage is not that significant.
And HP is more important early on, I would say.
Should I blow that up?
No, I'm gonna save my bomb.
Nah, nah, I'm gonna see what's in there.
Could be a bomb in there, right?
Well, there you go.
That was a bomb in there.
Uh-oh.
Not that kind of gym.
This is the bad gym.
All right.
Again, I keep getting this item as well.
It's a shitty item.
It is what it is.
Should I go in?
No, I should not go in there.
That's a horrible idea.
There's also a button.
Lots of back-up hearts, I guess, if I take damage.
That's nice.
Oh, man.
Speak enough.
Yoink.
Oh, no.
Wow.
No way!
We got lucky there.
Huge.
Blasting cap.
No, I hate that.
No, thanks.
I don't want that.
A key.
Man, this is just... bad.
Oh, no.
Wait, how did you just take so much damage?
Was it my familiar?
Did you actually help me a lot?
It was the damaging creep, I guess.
Right rage.
Speed and range.
Good.
That's actually huge on this character.
Ah, wait, it's not attack speed.
I thought it was attack speed.
But speed is still good.
Speed is huge.
But if I get attack speed on this one, you know, then we're talking because my extra damage can really add up.
Oh, yo.
Risky.
And scary at the same time.
Yeah, we got to do this.
I'm too scared.
Oh, I have pretty sick range, actually.
Hey, nice.
Ah, it's a big room.
This is going to be scary, isn't it?
Fuck!
Yeah, walk into my creep, nerds.
Let me put some creep here as well.
Nice.
Wow.
That's unfair!
There were no spikes on it, man.
That's bullshit.
Bullshit.
What the fuck is that?
Come on.
That's just unfair.
That's not even fun.
I mean, at least show the fucking spikes on the thing before I open it.
You know, like, that is just stupid.
It's like saying here, you enter a room, there's a 50% chance you're just going to take 50 damage, you know?
Wow.
That's fun.
Like, that was a decent run, and everything just went to shit because of that.
There we go.
Definitely taking this first.
Be good, please.
Okay, damage is good.
Large damage bonus must have much shorter range.
This is like shotgun mode.
And since I'm very low HP, it's going to be risky, but very rewarding, I think.
High risk, high reward.
I would love to get the Bible, actually.
Holy shit, we gotta save for the Bible.
Yeah.
I'm coming back.
Definitely.
We gotta find some money.
It's not looking good for money.
The damage is good now.
It is good.
It's very good.
I can go get the money now, actually, if I break open the piggy bank.
I'm going to wait a bit.
Oh, fuck me.
Oh, good.
Sloth!
Is that the guy that throws bombs?
Let's spawn to these guys.
Good damage.
Double Isaac's bombs.
Oh, that's actually not super good right now.
I would love a couple more bombs before I use that.
But now we're going to go get a crazy item.
Wait a minute, let me think.
There is an issue here.
The Bible is good, but it's going to replace my current one, and my current one is really good as well.
So the question is, is it going to be worth it?
I think yes, because we got damage upgrade, right?
So it's fine.
I'm doing it.
I'm taking the Bible, baby.
Being able to fly is going to help us for sure.
Like, it's got to be good, you know?
Actually, I could take a look in here just to see.
Alright, I took a look.
I'm leaving.
No, thanks.
That is not in my cards.
Let me try and use the Bible against this guy, see if that works.
Get Bible, nerd.
Okay, didn't do anything.
Maybe it works against Satan.
Yo!
Obviously it would.
He's like the ultimate evil guy.
Ultimate anti-Bible man.
Oh God.
Dude, my damage is pretty damn good right now.
That's some serious damage.
Man, fuck off with your matchbook.
Where's my health?
Man.
Fine, I'll take that.
I guess bombs are good.
And now I can do this one, and oh, you know what?
I'm going to wait with my two of clubs.
I'm going to find a shit ton of bombs, and I'm going to multiply them by two.
Okay, okay.
Let's just take a peek in here.
I'm taking a peek.
I'm leaving.
Don't even poop that green stuff at me if you're planning on it.
Whoa, what's that?
Wait, I've had this.
Tears, range, spiral.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Holy range.
I mean, that is... I have too much range.
This could be good, though.
Let's try it for a bit.
Okay.
It was actually perfect for this room.
But I would love to find those... You know what?
I'm still going to go for this strategy.
Take this first, find a bunch of bombs, duplicate them, and then we change it.
That is the strategy.
How dare you spawn spiders, huh?
Good.
Man, I love the view here.
Look at this.
We got fire in our butt.
What is making that happen?
Oh, is it the matchbook?
Or maybe the match?
One of them for sure.
That's a butt.
Mega Bean!
That's so good!
Brother, I mean, come on.
Why are you giving me all these good ones now?
I actually forgot about the Mega Bean.
Okay, my current tier list on Actives is going to be Converter and then Mega Bean.
Oh, and Bible.
Bible is, of course, also up there.
Forgot about the Bible, too.
Other than that, everything else sucks.
You heard it here first.
I could have pushed that up.
I was not fast enough.
Oh, man, the way they move around is creeping me out.
Don't like that.
All right.
Well, that's a boss.
Let's see.
Let's go check out the shop.
Oh, no, I want that!
Rip!
I can't get it.
That's so sad.
A tragedy.
Do I want to buy that?
No.
What was the other thing I had?
I had two of Clops and then something else.
I forgot what it was, but I wanted to change it out.
Let's just use it.
This one.
Six bombs now.
And then grab that one.
I think it'll pay off.
It looks weird, but think about it like this.
It's pretty much like a... what do you call it?
A diagonal attack, which is very good, you know?
Maybe I can get ranged down.
If I find ranged downpills, I'll actually eat them.
I mean, look at that shit.
That is just incredible.
Oh, wow.
Beautiful.
And I?
Glass?
Oh, extra damage?
More lock?
Whoa!
Oh, you want me to go in there and do things?
I don't think so, game.
But I will have a look.
Contract decreases the likelihood of a boo.
Wait, is that the same one?
No, that's Guppy's tail.
This one is... No, all this sucks ass.
Boo!
Nobody likes that.
It's horrible.
Can I please hit that up there?
How do I?
I can't hit the fucking flames!
Alright, fine.
I guess I won't do that.
Okay.
Not that way, this way.
Oh,
it's kind of awkward that I can't sort of shoot opposite.
It's only my... yeah, okay.
Maybe this is not the best.
Then it's gonna be a little awkward at times.
I'm gonna do this while I can.
Pills.
Bombs a key, okay.
Oh my god, it changed my bombs and keys.
That's what that does.
It flipped them.
Oh.
That was close.
It's gonna be a problematic situation.
Oh, thanks.
That's what that does.
Man, this Ouroboros thing is really awkward, I gotta admit.
Like, sometimes it is amazing, mostly.
Not that good.
It's super awkward.
I need to find another trinket ASAP.
Are you not getting hit by that?
Brother!
Okay.
Pride!
You're gonna blow yourself up?
Oh, I guess you don't care about that.
Ow!
Wow.
Be that way.
Not bad.
You need some getting used to this for sure.
Just more?
Yeah.
Man, what a weird layout.
Another big room and then hopefully a secret somehow.
Spectral tiers are pretty cool, though.
Ooh.
Huge.
What's that?
More luck?
Converged bad pills?
Yay!
And then there also was a little bit of extra.
Chance of getting room clear increases chance of winning rewards from bombs?
Arcade games?
Bombs, huh?
Wait, which ones are the bombs?
We got the beggars?
That's the one with the coins.
Bombs could be... Let me think.
What do bombs do?
What do they want?
Do they want bombs or keys?
None of that makes sense to me.
Health?
Do they want to steal my blood?
I'm actually not sure what the bombs is.
What even is a bomb?
I mean, I know the expression bomb and smoke, you know?
Could be bomb-related?
Bro, please die!
Thank you.
The stars.
Teleport to treasure room.
Wait.
If there is a planetarium, teleport to it instead.
I mean, maybe there is?
There's not, I guess.
I would love to see the planetarium.
I have never seen it, though.
Also, I'm still at 1 HP, which is problematic.
I do have money.
What's that?
Bombs, purse.
I was too trinkets to be held at time.
Sponsor random trinkets!
Oh, I like that.
No money, though.
Maybe.
No.
He rolls all items and pickups in the room.
Ooh.
Jara flies.
Eh, okay.
That was not worth it.
That was a waste of money.
Poli Sephirolus.
Never seen this guy.
That's a new one.
Also, I'm going to die for sure.
Get banished to the Shadow Realm.
I command thee.
Like, how am I going to... How did I actually dodge that?
That was crazy.
How did I win?
What the fuck, man?
More range?
I don't think so.
It's too much range.
I mean, it's sort of... The more range I get, the more diagonal my initial shot becomes, you know?
Radius gets larger on that circle.
Moving on.
No hearts for me, either.
That's just sad.
Could I not buy a heart?
Was there not even a heart I could buy?
Wish me luck.
I mean, we got keys.
Okay, that's pretty cool.
That's not going to heal me, though.
Unless I can eat the keys.
Okay, lock in now.
This is going to be tough.
Half an HP.
That was good, that was good.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Bum alert, bum alert.
Man.
Imagine what I could do with one more HP.
One more heart.
That's all I'm saying.
Shit.
Oh, but wait, I can fly!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, that's massive.
It bombs.
Huge.
Lovely wings, too.
That was massive.
How am I going to deal with you?
Alright, that works.
Oh, look at this!
Man, we are just keying it up this time around, huh?
That was the freest door of all doors.
The Empress.
That's good.
I cannot fly over there and grab that, unfortunately.
Not yet, but I could in a moment.
Would you look at that?
Massive.
Wow!
We got to get flight ASAP.
What's that?
That tooth?
Firing crates and aura around Isaac.
No, it's not even... I thought it was a trinket.
Too bad.
More options.
I'm going to blow you up.
Man, we gained demon and angel by doing that.
I could place bombs here, but then there's going to... We need a bit more mana here.
Now, to get to that guy, I need to... here and then here.
Right?
That works.
Never mind!
We found this instead.
Should I gamble here?
I'm going to blow it up.
I was hoping for money.
No!
Okay.
Well, how the hell do I get in there, then?
It's not meant to be, maybe.
Not bad at all.
Time for the boss.
I could go and do, you know, the last room, but... dark one.
Let's try the Bible here.
Didn't do shit.
He looks pretty demonic, though.
I was hoping that it would work.
Oh, God.
Wow!
I can't hit him.
It may be over.
Somehow it's not.
Somehow we're still... One health!
Huge business.
That's what we like to see.
Finally.
I think we move on.
Just move on.
Oh, that guy died.
Please die, please die, please die.
Thank you.
Let's go here.
Oh, that's evil down there.
Oh, wow.
Nice.
Poop!
Bot bombs!
Toxic blast, plus five bombs.
Explosions, damage, and concuss all enemies.
That sounds pretty nice.
Let's try it.
Well, they all died.
Buying this heart would be pretty good, I guess.
Three blue flies.
Or we get a randomized bag.
I'm tempted to do that, actually.
Trust it's gonna be better.
It wasn't.
I gambled, kids!
It's not worth it.
Gambling bad.
Wow.
He's gonna jump.
I have
to remember that I can fly.
If I see a room where it's needed.
Cheers.
We got a beggar.
I mean, he's not gonna get my money.
Not today.
Sorry, I don't have any money on me.
Unidentified, we love those.
Haha!
Very nice.
Oh, we also have the Empress, which does more damage.
That's good.
I gotta remember that.
That was close.
Amazing.
Wrath!
That's gonna be easy with this setup here.
Boom.
We keep going north.
That's close!
Man, I will never figure it out.
My best bet about that at some point is to get an item description that mentions it.
Money.
Shit!
Wow!
Man, that guy's crazy!
What can you even do against that evil?
Kill him.
Okay, okay.
Get poisoned.
Come on.
Scary.
I need some more HP, though.
Oh, he was not dead!
There we go.
I do have money now.
I should go back to the shop.
I don't remember what they had there.
But I think they had some good stuff that I could use.
Yeah, okay.
I'm gonna get this thing.
I think we need it.
Play it safe.
Totally worth.
If only I had a converter.
Why doesn't that spawn all the time?
Wrong way.
That's with my mouth, anyway.
Look at my mouth.
I have a crazy, like, lower bite or whatever it's called.
Oh, wait.
I'm going the wrong way again.
All right, here we go.
War?
Let's try the Bible.
Doesn't do anything.
Dude, how crazy is it that I managed to figure that out with Mom?
Like, I just happened to have the Bible, and I was like, let's go fly.
You know?
I'm so... Like, how many other things are going to be in this game like that?
That's crazy.
Fuck!
Wow, he was fast.
Cube of Meat is fucking useless.
I hate this item.
Honestly, I hate all of this.
There's enemies in here!
Jesus.
All right, all right.
Moving on.
I saw my life flash before my eyes just now.
Okay.
Ah, you're not getting my HP.
Absolutely not.
Uh-oh.
Wow!
Man.
Please give me another trinket!
For Christ's sake!
Jesus!
Okay, that's actually good.
I can fly!
Mega worth.
Amazing.
I'm going to save this for a store.
Please don't shoot me.
Fuck!
Impossible!
Oh!
The random bullshit hitting me is horrible.
I lost my amazing heart.
Wait, I have a feeling.
It's very strong.
It's at 78.
Come on!
Never trust a feeling.
Ah, should I get this?
I think so.
Thanks!
See you later!
Oh my god.
At least we have 2 HP.
That's twice the amount I normally have.
That's very nice.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, stay in the corner!
Stay in the corner!
Force field of toxic bullshit.
Get in the corner!
Stop with the bomb!
Okay, here.
Here.
Oh, man!
What the heck?
Uh, I can fly.
I don't know if I should waste it here, though.
It's not that hard to dodge.
Yeah, there we go.
Uh-oh.
Not these hanged men.
Oh god, oh god, oh god!
No!
Get in the corner!
Poison go!
No, I can't get that hard!
Oh wait, I can.
I'm getting it.
I think it's worth.
More toxic stuff?
I've had that before.
That's actually pretty good.
A ladder.
Building bridges.
Oh, no way!
Really?
Yeah!
Cool.
Very nice.
That sounds hella useful.
I'm gonna blow him up.
I gained a little bit on demon and angel.
For some reason.
Oh my god, really?
Look at this!
Oh, that's amazing!
Very cool.
I cannot make bridges over spikes, huh?
Too bad.
Wow, this is not easy.
Somehow I did that without losing any HP.
I'm honestly in shock.
I'm gonna grab this full heart.
Huge!
Now we gotta nail this.
Oh shit, it's mom!
Okay, we're not gonna nail it.
Unless we use the Bible.
I have no mana!
Rip mana!
Wait, why is mom doing that?
Mom is weird.
Mom, why do you like this?
Also, I lost my special heart.
Mom?
Oh, you got me there?
No way!
Fuck!
How come mom was acting that way, though?
That's crazy.
Like, okay, this character is way too hard, man.
I can't win anything on that.
I feel like this character right here, man.
Judas is fucking difficult.
Wow.
It is like next level.
Didn't I unlock something else?
Oh wait, there was something else that I unlocked.
Let me see.
Secrets.
No, I need to go to- can I not see the latest?
Oh, that's useless, then.
I'm not gonna sit there and scroll through everything.
I wish it would show me the latest.
Uh, let's go with something else.
What do I want now?
Wait a minute, what is Eden tokens?
Three.
Also, wait, is that on greed?
I didn't mean to do that.
Uh, let's do Eden?
That was a pretty good character, right?
Oh yeah, we start with random items on this one.
Monstro's tooth to slam down on a random enemy?
That's a pretty good one.
Plus one damage and range?
Oh, not bad.
And a AAA battery.
Cool.
Let's get to it.
Oh man, I have such a low shoot rate- uh, rate.
Look at this.
Like, I'm holding the button right now.
This is me holding the button.
Yikes.
That's pretty bad.
In fact, it may even be useless.
We
gotta find some attacks for each stat, like... paramount importance.
Oof.
That's rough.
Uh, no, I'm getting the treasure room.
And then we do, mom.
I mean, the first boss.
You know what I mean.
Like, this room is fucking insane.
I can barely outrun them.
Holy shit, bro.
Give
me that.
I also lost my other heart, so now I'm playing on one heart again.
Except this time, just much worse.
Start.
Please die.
Thank you.
What is that?
Please be attack speed.
Party time?
Bozo?
What does Bozo mean?
More damage, a soul heart.
Chance to briefly apply fear or charm to an enemy?
Chance to spawn a rainbow poop on the ground when taking damage.
Okay, but why is that good?
Why is rainbow poop good?
What's the point?
Okay, I get a brief animation.
Cool.
Showing a rainbow.
Pills.
Some money here?
No money.
Okay, donate everything.
The machine broke.
After four donations.
Uh, go back up.
Time for the boss.
I also somehow look like, uh, what's her name?
Harley from MCU or whatever.
You know what I mean?
Like the superhero people.
Dingle.
Why did you hit them and not the boss?
Stupid Monstro.
Oh my God.
My character's not even fast enough to dodge.
Wow.
Oh, that was tough.
More health is very welcome.
This is gonna be a tough one, guys.
If I don't find some kind of miracle item that gives me a million attack speed, it's pretty much just over.
Okay.
Oh, those are very annoyingly placed.
Oh my god, really?
Come on!
Good!
He's in love?
Come here.
Oh, you man.
Yeah, okay.
I'm actually glad I died.
Fuck this run.
That was absolutely horrible.
Let's see here.
Dead Sea Scrolls triggers another active item effect chosen at random.
Cloud Familiar that follows Isaac and spawns a trail of damaging blue creep.
Enemies that touch the cloud have a chance to be struck by a damaging light beam.
I like the sound of that.
Random bullshit, go!
I gain damage.
Ow.
Wait, we only have one heart again?
Bro.
I'm finna just pick a character with some HP after this.
Fuck this, man.
Mass fear.
Mom's past!
Temporarily inflicts fear on all enemies and spawns a blue fly.
That is... alright?
Cool?
I mean, we're gonna use that when shit hits the fan.
I like it.
Use it!
Yeah, run away.
You don't wanna see none of this.
You don't want none of this.
But it's not addictive.
Still no keys, no bombs, no money, no nothing.
And a terrible haircut as well.
Does it get worse?
At least we have decent damage this time around.
Or attack speed, I mean.
Like, you can work with this, at least.
Well, that was a short one.
No money for the shop either?
What a tragedy.
Just wanna see if there's maybe a bit of money here.
A coin.
That's for you.
Time to kick the boss's ass with half an HP.
Oh, that's actually tough.
I may die here.
This boss is crazy.
Wow, I got lucky there.
He stopped right in front of me.
There's not enough depression with this cloud.
Yeah, okay.
Man, I have had it with characters that have no HP.
Fuck that.
Let's go back to something with a lot of HP.
I'm tired of having one HP constantly.
Lazarus.
There was also, like, something I needed to do with Lazarus, right?
Let's see.
Oh, wait, unlocked by beating Greed Mode with Azazel!
Hold on now!
We're doing Greed Mode with Azazel!
Any excuse to do Azazel, I'll take it.
And then we can also be reminded how this works.
Ooh, holy shit.
That's a lot of 15 casts here.
We can reroll.
There's a chest over there.
He wants keys.
Okay.
I guess we start by going in here, right?
Nice.
And we don't have a key yet.
We will soon.
Beating Greed Mode, huh?
What does that entail?
Holy shit.
Okay.
We did it.
No keys, though.
But maybe we can buy one.
Yes, we can.
I can buy one key and one item here.
Placenta is pretty good.
And we can go in here.
What's that?
Chocolate milk!
Chart shots?
Replaces tears with a chart shot that increases in size and damage the longer it is held.
Huh?
It's over.
This is fucking useless.
What is the speed on that recharge?
Oh, no.
At least that's a lot of damage, I guess.
Pretty good against bosses, then?
Fucking get nuked.
Yeah, pretty good against bosses.
All right.
Got some more money.
No bombs.
I can't buy bombs in there?
I don't want to reroll, I think.
I think I want placenta when I can afford it.
What the hell?
I mean, that is a lot of damage.
I will admit.
Whoa.
Cool.
Whoa, look at this.
No way.
Black powder on this one.
Ooh.
I mean, we do need tears.
Tears is very important right now.
I'm taking it.
I think it's worth.
Because we're going to go get placenta later.
And it's going to be fine.
That was it for this floor or what?
I guess so, right?
There's this room, but I have the full.
We're chilling.
Uh-oh.
I'm playing it safe.
All right.
Shit.
Oh, well, we're not going to be able to... whatchamacallit, buy the placenta, I guess, then.
We have no bombs either.
Oh, I could just go in here.
Ah, but no keys.
Let me do it.
Trust.
Four.
Okay, moving on.
Wait, there's enemies.
Man, the charge speed is rough.
So I guess by beating this place, you've got to get to the last level, right?
That's how you beat it.
Let me go in here.
That box.
Fuck off!
Fuck's sake.
I found pills.
Uh, magician is ranged.
Actually, that's huge.
The keys also pretty good.
What is this thing?
Calus, your feet feel stronger?
Grants immunity to damage from spikes and creep.
Okay.
That is pretty good, but I'm flying already, so does it matter?
I don't know if it does.
Uh, I don't know if I should pick that heart up until the very end.
It's too risky to have it on now.
The mulligan.
Chances spawn a bluefly each time a shot.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Okay, let's go.
Wait, how am I ever supposed to do this with the timer?
Like, I'm too slow at dealing damage here.
I just can't do any damage in time.
I guess it worked.
Good.
No, I didn't hit him.
Massive.
Ahoy!
Pretty cool.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do here.
Like, I can maybe get this.
It's more ranged, right?
And then we have, what's this?
Ooh, shot speed.
Oh wait, shot speed is useless to me, right?
It is the shot or tiers that I want.
So I have more charge.
I can also re-roll things.
Mom's bracelet.
A lump of coal.
How is that gonna affect my beam?
And then I question mark.
Okay.
I need a bit more money.
Whoa, look at this guy.
He's dead.
Okay.
20 gold.
I'm gonna try this.
Sprinkles!
What is that?
Places a stationary turret?
And fire shots in a rotating pattern for the rest of the room.
Pretty cool.
Shots copy most of Isaac's tier effects.
That sounds really good, actually.
Very nice.
I could also gamble, but nah.
Probably shouldn't write.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, he was immune.
Because it's the ghost guy.
Foreskin man.
Wow!
You got wrecked, son!
Impressive.
I didn't even use my turret.
Well, we didn't gain any money.
That's it, huh?
Should I spend my money or save it?
I think I'll save it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh no, the poop came out.
Okay, we go down here first.
That's good.
More tiers and range.
That's exactly what we need.
Oh, wait a minute.
I... Oh no, I didn't grab the heart!
I fucking saved it specifically for this.
Dammit.
I could have had one more extra HP right now.
Damn.
All right.
What do we have in here?
A spoon?
A potato peeler?
A very cheap key.
Thanks.
I'll take it.
In fact, I should maybe buy two of them, since they're so cheap.
For the next floor, right?
The wafer!
That's a pretty damn good one!
Lovely.
Wait, we have the magician.
I have to remember this.
Okay, here we go.
Huh?
How did I just take damage randomly?
Like, I click the button, instantly take damage.
How's that fair?
And boom!
Okay.
It's like that, huh?
A lot of money.
Do I want to buy anything, though?
I can maybe re-roll a little bit.
Shit!
Okay.
Guess I'm getting... spoon.
Or this one.
No, no, no, wait.
No, fuck that.
Wait, permanent cube of meat?
If I get that along with a... Oh, this is a way to get, like, a lot... the stages of the cube of meat.
Yeah.
But I can't do that.
I'm taking this.
A bit of speed is always nice.
Oh yeah, I forgot about the turret.
Let's try the turret.
Oh, sick!
It's shooting my laser.
Whoa!
Holy angel!
I destroyed that angel.
Angel had no chance.
Okay.
I think I'm done buying here.
Let's see if I forgot something in here.
I didn't.
Not this time!
Okay, here we go.
This guy again?
What's up, dude?
You have the good light?
I have the evil light.
Oh man, then you do diagonal, huh?
Ahhh!
Huh?
Krampus!
Okay.
Next tier is increase in damage and size.
That's good, I think.
But how is that going to affect me?
Let's see.
I don't think it has any effect.
Yeah, that's pretty much
it.
Should we pill it up?
Oh!
Power pill!
Invincibility and contact damage.
Every two enemies killed heals Isaac.
Inflaked fear as it can't shoot.
Wish me luck!
That's horrible.
Oh well.
Oh no, we're going into the womb.
Or worse.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So if I put this down here, it's just going to stay here, right?
I'm going to put it here.
Oh wait, we go in here first.
Moms, pearls, range and luck.
And a soul heart!
That's actually pretty massive.
Dead Eye grants a stacking damage bonus for each successive shot that hits an enemy.
Very nice.
Oh man, it doesn't stay, okay.
I thought it was permanently on this floor.
That's too bad.
Drive by.
Yes, yes.
Oh crap.
Time is out, what then?
Maybe it's, you earn more money the faster you kill them.
Where are you?
Oh.
These don't disappear.
How do I damage you?
Okay, there we go.
Oh wait, they keep spawning new ones every time timer goes down.
So irregardless of how many are left.
Oh man, I'm going to die here.
Man, that was close.
I think we have hit the end here.
I can't survive.
Umbilical court replaces that one.
I guess it's better.
I don't need immunity from spikes.
Oh, maybe.
Yeah, I don't need that.
So umbilical court, entering a room with half red heart or less, gain a little, but I don't have any red hearts.
It's better than what I had though.
26 money.
Huge.
Absolutely massive.
Bar of soap is more tears.
That would be good, but man, I need HP.
Damn.
I guess I'm getting this.
I can charge much faster now.
That should definitely help a lot.
And we have a turret.
I guess I'll save that for the boss.
Whoa.
Damn, son.
Where the hell?
Uh-huh.
There you are.
You got no more steed, huh?
Okay, not bad.
Speed and even more damage.
Oh man, we're becoming a glass cannon here.
I'm taking it.
Ooh!
Maybe I can afford it after the next wave, or is it boss time?
It's boss time.
So we're gonna put this down.
Oh my god, it's the heart.
That's crazy.
Wow, dude.
Caught down!
Fuck!
What a way to die.
Yeah, consolation prize.
Thank you.
I really need this now.
Thanks.
Gain some shot speed, I guess.
All right.
That was a crazy way to die.
Okay, what do we have here?
Pentagram.
Ooh, that's pretty damn good.
It's cheap too.
We're going for it.
And even this.
Yoink.
Here we go.
Why did I take damage, for fuck's sake?
Why did I just lose half a heart?
I'm so mad about this shit.
What just happened?
For Christ's sake.
Oh, there's spikes on the button.
That's probably what that is.
Faster.
Good.
That was a lot of money.
I need this.
Yeah.
Oh, this one is also... Oh!
Holy crap.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah, we're back.
Money me.
No money for me.
I'm going to try and get a key with the next money here.
Where are you?
Shit!
That was the worst spot.
Wait, go in.
Go up here.
Wait, what was this?
Dude, should I get this or the key?
Man, I'm getting this, I think.
This, I know what I'm getting, right?
The key, I may not know what I'm getting.
That's my argument.
Hold on, there's a chest!
Duck tape.
Let me, I'll take it.
That seems bad.
Like, it seems worse than not having anything.
Am I crazy?
I'm taking this.
Magic gate pole.
Okay, we're just going to not go in there.
At least I know what I'm getting now.
So here's the thing.
It says 10 out of 10 on coins.
I'm not sure what that means.
But it's like the weird type of coin.
It's not the real coin.
Oh, more pills.
Ew.
Range up!
Massive.
Time for the boss.
Why are there no spikes on the stupid button now, all of a sudden?
Ah, we can go in here!
Oh, we can also go in here!
Oh wait, no.
I'm an idiot, I thought it was an angel room.
I thought they both spot.
Rip.
But you know what?
Maybe that's actually a good thing.
It means I'm not going to sacrifice another red heart like I did last time.
Yeah, it's actually better.
Oh, unknown.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Oh, that's huge.
Fuck yeah.
Now I know I have three black, two red.
Wow, that was close.
Going pretty well.
All right, well...
Nice.
Okay, uh, we go in here.
What's that?
I don't know what that is.
We know what that is, though.
Ooh, more speed could be good.
So, bombs.
Money.
A heart as well, if I need it.
I don't think I need that now.
I think this heart may be worth it, the blue one.
We can go for speedball and then the heart.
Or we take this unknown.
Let's take the unknown.
Allow six weeks for delivery.
Coupon.
Makes one item in the shop or Devil Room free.
Selected at random.
Holding this item passively guarantees that one item in the shop will be on sale.
Ah!
That's why this one suddenly had half.
Cool.
Well, well, well.
Oh,
it's the heart that went free?
Come on.
Need to die!
There we go.
Okay, we don't have enough mana, though, to do things with this yet.
I'm gonna buy a key, I think.
What was that one?
Probably recharges the held active.
Okay, let's do it.
Wish me luck.
What is that?
Multidimensional baby!
What was that?
Yodup buddy?
That was the opposite of buddy.
Familiar that follows Isaac's movements on a delay.
Frontleaf tears that pass through.
It's are doubled and gain increased range and shot speed.
Ha!
Oh, that sounds like a skill thing.
There's He's straight on top of me.
Unless I can somehow...
Wait, what's the point?
Am I getting the effect of this?
I've never seen this guy either.
It's a new one.
Whoa!
He just stole some of my money.
He's farting on me.
He did not enjoy losing.
Oh, that's a... that's an angel room.
It's the Bible.
I think I'll take... Ah, will I take that?
Will I take that?
I feel like the one I have right now is kind of crazy for whatever's going on.
But the Bible could be kind of huge, because it's the freaking Bible, right?
Oh, give me that.
Should I take this?
Nah, I'm gonna leave it.
I think we have something cool going right now.
I don't want to ruin it.
No money, though.
Wait, did we go in here?
Yeah, yeah, okay.
I could go in here, but the problem with the sasal is... I'm not gonna win.
Give me the money.
Okay.
Things
are looking up.
White room first.
Very nice.
Range is huge.
Look at this.
That's gonna help a ton.
How, man?
Nice.
Oh, shit.
Wow.
I think I just messed it up, because I didn't do it in time.
We lost all of our black hearts as well, unfortunately.
Let's see if we can make something free.
Oh, shit.
Massive.
Wait, nothing new is gonna spawn there?
Oh, wait, is the... Can I somehow use this freaking knife?
Clicking all the buttons.
Oh, fuck, I'm an idiot.
Well, that's a spiky chest.
Fuck that noise.
No, thanks.
Ah, I honestly don't want anything except this.
Maybe the... No, I'm not gonna... I'm gonna save my money, actually.
Mom's bottle of... Hey, that's huge.
Oh, horrible.
Good.
You.
Oh, what is this shit?
This is demonic as hell.
There's no timer on this one, though.
Nice.
Nothing special opened for me, unfortunately.
Now, I could try and buy this.
Grants plus one soul heart at the start of each new floor.
I mean, that is pretty good, I guess, for me.
Reveal secret... Are there even secret rooms in this place?
I could gamble.
Come on, money.
Hey, sick.
I just need one more money.
Should I open this chest?
Chance of... Yeah.
Huge.
Let's try this here.
There is a frickin' secret here!
Wow!
Incredible.
Is this my room?
I kind of want to bomb the bed.
Is there a monster under the bed?
Maybe a hidey hole under the bed?
I don't have a bomb, though.
Shit.
This interesting.
Okay, time for the boss.
My damage is not super good.
I honestly don't even know what these tiny hearts do, but I killed them anyway.
I'm scared of what they may do.
Man, I'm so close to getting hit constantly.
Yeah, okay, man.
Okay, man.
Oh, wait a minute.
What's that?
Ooh!
Dude.
Hmm.
Is it worth... Ooh, nine extra lives!
Oh, my god.
Both of these are actually kind of sick.
Oh, man.
I think I'm gonna go with the brimstone, man.
Infinite range.
Can you imagine?
Two black hearts?
Oh, I signed a deal with the devil.
I fucked myself, I think.
This is really bad.
I'm not gonna survive this.
Ew.
Oh, man.
This may have been a mistake.
My tech was already fine.
Why am I so greedy?
Okay, we're in the womb now.
Let's see what we got in here.
Hey, massive.
Very good.
Evil fire.
Get rid of it.
What's that?
Oh, my god.
Massive.
That means we're gonna get a key.
We need a key.
Let's go in here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Is this the good one?
No, mini mush.
I don't need range.
See, if I had the old attack, I could have had more range.
I wasted.
I shouldn't have bought the frickin brimstone.
It was a mistake.
And again, I mean, infinite range is kind of crazy.
Let's not kid ourselves.
It is really good, man.
It is.
It is really good.
In fact, it may actually be worth it.
Whoa.
Did you see that just now?
Oh, wait.
Is it because we're passing through our friend?
So that guy... there's more.
Time out went off.
Yeah, I think it just spawns more enemies.
Sick.
Let's go make something free.
Come on.
Wait, wait.
Sick.
Absolutely massive.
It doesn't respond, though.
Unfortunately, I could buy like four blue hearts if I wanted.
50% chance to drop a pickup when taking damage.
That could be huge as well.
I need a key, though.
Key.
And then we're gonna get this.
Grab and pick up a rock.
Press an attack button to throw.
No, that's not very good, is it?
Let's go open this first.
Unfortunately, no two items.
Depression.
Why not?
Now with the remaining I have.
I can always come back and buy the blue heart again, I guess, if I need to.
And I kind of want to refresh things in here.
So I guess I got to buy this.
Wait, what?
Oh, okay.
Do I want that on me?
I kind of want to take this next time I get seven, but I also want to maybe save for the blue.
Whoa!
Bro, I can't see what's happening.
I can't fucking see things off screen!
The room layout here is really annoying.
Why'd it have to be vertical and not horizontal?
Really annoying.
Oh, secret room up here.
No bombs, though.
Oh, maybe this is a bomb?
Mama Mega, boom!
This item is consumed to spawn a massive shockwave that deals huge damage and destroys all breakable objects in the room.
The shockwave reverberates once through every room entered for the remainder of the floor.
Can break open time hardened walls?
Okay.
That sounds pretty damn cool.
I'm so scared.
I'm going to pick this up first in case I take damage from this.
We also have milk or something else.
Okay.
Oh, wait, no, no.
I picked up the bomb.
Wish me luck.
Damn.
Wow.
Everything did well.
The shockwave, I guess.
What is this room?
Huh?
Why would I spend time in there?
Oh, my gosh.
Shockwave.
Okay.
Didn't break any walls in here.
I could go in there and check, but nah.
Kind of pray that I hit something.
Where are you?
There you are.
That's right.
You're done.
Oh, we can go in here.
All right.
What's this?
The Book of Sin spawns a random pickup.
Got peace caller.
Three, bro.
Oh, I think no.
It's I'm taking this though.
I think it's better.
Like for this game mode, it's especially insane.
Oh, wait a minute.
What?
Oh, yeah.
It still counts for this floor, even though I don't have the item on.
That's funny.
Oh, my God.
We're in shield.
Man, shield as hell.
Whoa.
Desert?
Oh, that's huge.
That's also huge.
Wait, they both do the same.
Which one is better?
I mean, instead of... wait.
It's both dog food.
I'm taking this.
We can go in here now.
Poop.
Plop.
It's actually just called the poop.
Oh, crap.
Spots of poop.
Oh, it's an active.
Huh?
All right.
No, thanks.
Not right now.
I guess it's good if you want to generate items when you destroy the poop.
Let's see what we have in here.
Oh, my God.
That is huge.
Yes.
Torn photo.
Shot speed.
Oh, look how fast I charge.
Oh, my God.
Incredible.
More hearts there.
Or we can... nah.
I want to come back and buy that.
Or make it free, potentially.
Oh, fuck.
What's happening?
I have no idea what just occurred.
Oh, you're still alive, you bastard.
I'm just gonna do this and hope I hit something.
This is the strategy, dude.
Just... just shoot up.
Hope for the best.
We're playing Space Invaders.
Space Invaders.
We did it.
Incredible.
It's free.
Whatever it is.
Extra card room.
Ice, it can hold two cards at once.
All future pill drops are replaced with cards.
I don't like that.
Spawns a random card on pickup.
All right.
That's a good card, though.
I'll take this.
And more shot speed.
More range is kind of useless for me, though.
So maybe I don't.
Maybe I don't.
I have two luck, right?
We should be lucky here.
Follow the zebra.
Cancer?
Huge!
I was about to say love cancer, but I... Oh, it's a trinket?
Huge.
That's actually pretty good.
Here we go again.
I like my strategy of just staying down here.
If I can.
Right now I can't, but...
Okay, that went pretty well.
I think I want to buy this anyway, just to get replacement.
Binky.
Soulheart size down.
Good.
Oh, that's a really good one.
Bro, I need that.
Can we get the money?
Somehow.
I doubt it.
There's also a secret room.
I need a bomb.
Boss time?
We got weird zombies or mummies.
That was huge.
I can go in here now.
Permanently removes 1 HP to grant three soul hearts.
That is worth it, I think.
Chance to drop a soul heart when taking damage.
Chance to drop a half red heart when killing an enemy.
Chance increased with luck.
I do have a lot of luck.
Hmm.
This could be pretty good right now, because I have two luck, right?
And I do take damage, but it's only a chance.
Hold on.
Destroy this version.
Honestly, I like both.
I like this one and the other.
Oh, wait a minute.
This isn't active.
I don't like that in that case.
Give me this.
Yeah, sweet suffering.
We're going for that one.
Can we find a bomb somehow?
I could refresh the shop when I have money, but I don't have money.
All right, moving on, I guess.
Too bad no bomb in here.
You know what we could do?
We could go in here and hope for a bomb.
Let's launch one heart.
Key bomb coin!
Yay!
Well, there you go.
Very good.
Become invincible.
Launch two red hearts.
I think this is the best still.
Let's go bomb the shit out of this room.
All right.
Ew.
We've got maggots in here, or I don't even know what that is on the floor.
Centipedes.
Disgusting.
Moving on, baby.
Moving on.
Wait, the shop?
Oh, wait, right.
Okay.
Can we get a bomb?
Perhaps.
Uh-oh.
Whoa!
Oh, my God.
I have the perfect character for this.
Damn, son!
What the frick?
Look at all the hearts!
All righty.
I mean, we're gonna... Oh, I can't use my special yet.
Wait, why is it closed?
Oh, there's still one left.
Oh, okay.
Wait, uh, hold on a minute.
This is weird.
Things are not normal here.
This is not a normal floor.
I can't leave.
Okay, I guess we do this.
Bomberman.
Whoa!
Look at me go, man!
Oh, crap.
Massive.
And now we also have the active ready.
Let's go nuts.
Why are bombs so lacking?
It's crazy.
Wish me luck.
Oh, that's good.
Empty red health.
Heal up.
I didn't just do that.
I thought it was one of the 10,000 other hearts on the fucking floor.
I hate myself.
That is amazing.
That is actually unbelievable what just occurred.
All right, let's keep it going here.
Oh, that's funny.
Man, the amplified laser here.
It's no joke.
Holy cannoli.
Hello.
Oh, wait, I'm immune to that, right?
Because I fly.
25 coin of Reno's.
I hate this sharp keep.
I really don't want it.
So instead, I'm gonna do this.
Aha!
Refreshes everything.
Two soul hearts.
Isaac can hold two pills at once.
Okay, so now we can hold two cards and two pills.
All future card drops are replaced with pills.
Man.
I think I like that more than the cards.
I will do it.
I'll do it.
Nice.
And...
Nice!
Oh, the eraser could be cool.
Bombs!
It's cheap!
Huge!
Very good.
Blow it up.
Oh, yeah.
Super magnet slowly pulls off.
That's not good enough.
Hold on a minute.
This could be interesting.
Let's see how that...
That is... that is pretty cool.
That is pretty damn cool.
But minus 33 tears.
Let me see what the difference is.
Honestly, it's a little slower, but the AoE is massive.
Then again, this is really good.
And I have infinite range and I can just move like this, right?
But if I move side to side with this, also it does give me other stuff.
Hold on.
There we go.
More range.
I mean, range doesn't matter, I guess.
Respectful tears, which I already have, I guess.
I think this is better.
I mean, I'm doing fine with this right now.
Oops, don't go in there.
Maybe it should go in there.
Like this, I can just sit here, you know?
We're chilling.
Amazing.
11 out of 10 coins.
I don't know what that means, man.
Whoa.
Okay, moving on.
Ultra Greed.
Huh?
Ultra Greed?
Oh!
All right, dude.
Ultra Greed!
That's, I guess, who this place is named after!
Oh, it's a giant-ass Greed!
That makes a lot of sense.
Wait, am I just really nice here?
Because I don't take damage from his stuff?
Oh my god!
Oh, I should not hit those coins, I guess.
The coins are bad.
I don't even know what's happening!
That's a lot of Greeds.
Wow!
Dude, what is happening?
This guy has so much HP, by the way.
I need to amplify my damage with the thing.
I kind of regret not getting the Ouroboros right now, because of all these ads.
If I had known these ads would be a thing.
Let me stand behind you, man!
Okay, come to me.
Come to me.
Play Space Invaders.
Cool.
I'm trying to shoot through my familiar here to deal more damage.
It's really difficult to do.
Oh, we got hearts on the floor!
There it is.
I got it.
Holy shit, bro.
Here he comes!
What the fuck?
Keep damaging him!
Yeah!
You, Lilith!
There we go, baby!
Wait, Greed.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's going on here?
Oh, I have no money.
Okay.
I'm gonna blow him up.
Can't blow you up.
Show me!
He looks so cute!
Did I just become one of those eternal freaking dolls that just sit everywhere?
Oh, that's creepy.
What the hell?
Okay.
We did it, and we unlocked the character we came here to do.
Or unlock.
Beautiful.
Let me see.
Which one was that?
That was Lilith.
Oh, it's Lilith.
I thought it said Eulith.
Incubus.
Cambian conception?
Cambian conception.
I don't know what that's supposed to mean.
Oh, shit!
I didn't mean to click.
I had my hands on the wrong part of the keyboard.
I guess we're gonna do this.
Hold on.
It's a duplicate of each... I don't even know which difficulty I just had, because I thought I had my three fingers on the arrow keys, but I had them near my space key or like enter key instead.
So I may have accidentally chosen a different difficulty.
I'm gonna exit the game.
Oh, you can resume a run?
That's kind of huge.
I had no idea you could do that.
Let me see.
Okay, I'm on hard.
That's kind of cool.
I didn't know.
I thought I had to finish a run.
That's pretty good.
I have to know.
Well, we did it.
We got a sure win, and then we got another sure win towards the end.
It was a win at the beginning.
Questionable actions throughout the middle.
Fantastic ending, I think.
Yeah.
Pretty good.
What's going on?
I know this was a bit of a surprise dream.
I hope it's okay.
I know you mostly want to be notified in time, but I really wanted to play, okay?
I'm sorry.
Oh, hold on.
Let me pull this over.
Have you thought about buying an eye tracker for an ice extreme?
Could be fun.
That could be fun, actually.
Maybe I should.
It don't cost much, right?
That could be fun, actually.
I'll think about it.
That sounds pretty interesting.
I don't know how well those work, though.
Is it actually like good?
It'll amplify the blindness.
I mean, maybe.
We'll see.
Guys, you're just gonna be more disappointed after the eye tracker.
You're gonna see me clearly look at things and then not do whatever it is I'm looking at.
I mean, think about the possibilities.
Either I do that, or I simply don't look at the things that I don't notice.
And what then?
What have you learned?
You have to remember, sometimes the eyes just dart across the screen in random places, right?
When you look around.
That's how you scan an area sometimes.
So even though, you know, the eye tracker may show something, it doesn't mean I necessarily saw it, right?
You will understand your thought process more.
I doubt it, but okay.
We will see.
I'm gonna look into it, see if I can buy one.
We learned that it is genuine, I guess.
I mean, I am not rage-baiting here, okay?
I don't know how many times I need to say that.
I am not playing worse on purpose.
Trust me, I want to win as much as you guys want me to win.
It's all I want.
I want to do this as best I can.
I'm not gonna fucking play worse on purpose.
That's stupid.
Ah, you know what, guys?
Fuck, you got me, man.
You got me.
It is on purpose.
I'm actually a really good gamer.
I'm just... every time I do something like that, it's on purpose, okay?
You gotta understand.
I need to make my money.
I gotta get my bag, right?
This is how I get my clicks and my comments on YouTube.
This is what I do, man.
Okay, so just know that I'm a god gamer, and every time I make a mistake, it's not because of me.
There you go.
Clipped and shipped.
Yeah.
Are you having fun still?
Does it look like I'm having fun?
I think it's pretty obvious that I'm having fun.
But yes, to answer your question.
By the way, I was kidding just now.
I am not, you know, purposefully rage-baiting.
That was one time.
Maybe a couple times.
But I feel like when I do it, it's very obvious when I do it on purpose, you know?
Like, for example, in blueprints.
I feel like that was obvious.
But it's like, why would anyone rage-bait about something that isn't funny?
It's like going up to someone and saying, hey, what's the time?
You know, they look at their watch and they straight up just lie.
They say, oh, it's three o'clock when it's actually five.
Like, rage-baiting?
Like, why would you do that?
It's not even fun to rage-bait like that.
At least make it fun when you rage-bait, if anything, right?
Also, honestly, regarding the blueprints thing, not to spoil anything, of course.
I don't want to spoil anything.
And don't spoil anything in the chat about it.
But I didn't originally intend to, like, with the purpose of rage-baiting, I just thought it was funny to do, right?
The thing I did without saying what I did.
But people thought it was rage-baiting, so it became, you know, it became that, I guess.
I just thought it was funny, right?
You're still midway through that series?
Do you know what I'm talking about then, Flash?
Or...
Like, it's obvious, no?
You must have seen it then, if you're halfway through.
I know a lot of people didn't think it was funny.
I think it was funny, and that's what matters.
I'm having fun with it.
By the way, guys, I need to say something.
Every time you guys say, oh, blind streamer, dementia, whatever the hell, right?
Oh, I can't believe you missed that, or what is going on here, rage bait, all that stuff.
I want to see you, okay, play this game blind, because this game is insane, by the way.
This game has so much stuff going on.
I want to see you play this game blind on stream for, I don't even know how many viewers are here, 200 viewers, knowing that people are watching, speaking a non-native language, trying to be somewhat entertaining at the same time, and do well, while you're speaking out loud,
saying everything that goes through your mind, and then have everyone criticize your gameplay, okay?
Trust me, it's not that easy.
If I booted up this game without chat, without anyone here, without being live, without having this in the back of my mind, without having to speak, all of that, I would do so much better, I think.
It's obvious, because I do get distracted, you know, it is a type of multitasking when I'm talking and playing.
It really is.
And if you don't believe me, try playing Starcraft 2 while talking, okay?
It is insanely difficult.
There's only a very few people who can do that at a high level, and one of them is eothermal, another is mana, liquid mana, and I guess also horsemen.
Those are like the three horsemen, you know?
It is insanely difficult to do.
And everyone misses stuff, right?
You just don't notice it yourself.
I just want to say that.
Now, I'm not going to deny that I may miss more than others, but it's not as bad as you guys make it out to me, it's all I'm saying.
And as long as I'm having fun, you know, who cares?
All of chat would do so good.
Yeah, it's the exact same thing with Starcraft.
Whenever you're streaming Starcraft, everyone in the chat is a grandmaster.
Or when someone's playing chess, everyone in the chat is a grandmaster, you know?
They know what to do.
But of course, in this game, if you have a thousand hours in this game, which I know some of you have, by the way, I know that.
I mean, you're gonna just automatically assume or like some things are just so natural to you that it's difficult for you to even put yourself in someone else's shoes that don't know anything about the game, right?
Speaking of Starcraft 2, did you saw this year's Minecraft first April snapshot?
I didn't?
Wait, what do you mean speaking of Starcraft 2?
How does that relate to... hold on a minute!
Talk to me itchy please.
Tell me more.
Tell me more immediately.
What do you mean?
Are you baiting me?
Dude, I was so close to saying next time we're playing the April thing.
You bastard.
I made a Minecraft April Fool's update where you just control a lot of blocks like minions.
Oh, okay.
That's already a thing though.
You can sort of take control of various mobs, you know, and see through their eyes.
Maybe it's just with the blocks now.
I've not watched Project Hail Mary.
You know what's funny?
I almost did it today.
Because the movie was playing at eight o'clock in my town.
And I thought, man, should I do it or should I play Isaac?
And then I was like, ah, if I go to the movies, I'm probably gonna get candy, right?
And that's not good for my diet right now.
I'm gonna fall off the wagon.
So I was like, ah, I'm not gonna do it.
I'm gonna go live instead.
So I was considering doing it today.
I may wait until it's out on DVD or whatever it's called.
Blu-ray.
Ah, but is it a movie I need to see in the cinema though?
Is it one of those?
Because I would consider Interstellar to be a movie that you, you know, should see in the cinema if you can.
Is it like good sound and good image and all that?
Cinematography and all that?
It's a long one?
Oh, that's good.
That always means I get my money's worth.
I feel good about watching long movies in the cinema.
Yeah, you know what's funny, Flash?
A lot of people in my feed as well talk about Hail Mary.
But you know what the best part is?
Nobody has spoiled anything.
Because I think everyone's liking it so much they don't want it.
Doesn't mean good quality.
No, but think of it like this.
If I go to an all you can eat buffet and I pay a certain amount of money and the food is shit, at least I'm happy I can eat a lot of it.
At least I'm getting a very full and I can stuff my pockets.
Not that I do that, but you know.
Unless the movie truly is shit.
Maybe I don't want to stay then.
It's long and good.
It's like having a big ass hot dog.
Hmm.
I see the I see the analogy.
I like it.
Yeah, exactly Rob Elf.
I have 50 wait how many hours do I have in this now?
Is it 50 hours already?
That can't be real.
It's more like 40 max, right?
But imagine me and like when I'm at 500 hours I'm gonna be fucking unstoppable.
I say that now.
Don't, you know, keep the receipts.
Don't bring up the receipts later.
I'm just saying.
I'm learning all the time, right?
I'm constantly seeing new things when I play this game.
Like last time I got into a whole new area.
The time before that I banished mom with a freaking Bible.
This time I met or I killed Satan and I went to the greed area and all kinds of shit happened, right?
Like so much stuff is happening.
I'm learning so much.
You should start making notes if you haven't already.
What notes though?
I'm not gonna sit here and take notes on every item because that already exists in the game, right?
If there's something that happens that warrants notes, I will do it.
Well, exactly.
So things I don't know or understand.
As soon as I see them, I will take notes if it warrants notes, right?
I don't know about Wrath of Maths.
I like math YouTube channels though.
Let me Google that.
Oh, Wrath of Math.
Okay.
No, I don't know about this one.
I teach math and rap sometimes.
Dude, that sounds like me.
Just I'm not very good at rapping.
Well, yeah, I'm definitely gonna take notes if it's something that I feel is needed later.
But for now, it's fine.
I'm doing okay.
Guys, thanks for watching.
This was a bit of a surprise stream out of nowhere.
I hope you enjoyed it.
I definitely did.
Thanks for showing up, enjoying it with me.
And yeah, Silksong is also out today.
Go check that out.
It's a banger.
I'll see you next time.
Good night.